<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-IL-Chicago-Database_Administrator.id01984391?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>9a1829213d5cd2243b4b61c3d28792d6</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Database Administrator</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Job Description Interactive Brokers Group, industry leader in direct access brokerage, is seeking a motivated Database Administrator to provide day-to-day production support for our highly automated mission critical systems. This position requires interacting with very technical users, big-picture analysis, and acute problem solving skills. Responsibilities • 24x7 Operational Support of production databases. • 9x5 Operations Support of Development/QA databases • Install, patch, and configure Oracle Software. • Automate day-to-day Database Administration activities. • On-Call after hours support as needed. • Provide first-level support of automated warning system Qualifications • 1-2 years experience as Oracle DBA in a production environment. • Backup and Recovery using Recovery Manager (rman). • Oracle 11g or 12c (at least 1 year) • Oracle 12c (ASM/RAC) • Oracle Applications (EBS) R12.2 (at least 1 year), including: o EBS Cloning o Patching using ADOP o WebLogic Server • Self-starter with initiative and desire to learn • Ability to work quickly in a fast-paced environment. • Ability to communicate clearly, constructively and concisely to peers and end-users.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01984391</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Information Technology| Database Administrator</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Database Administrator</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Chicago, IL, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Chicago</city>
      <state>IL</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-IL-Chicago-Financial_Advisor_Services_Representative_IL.id01977059?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>ec5d551e3307f0327dc85c43e055efc9</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Financial Advisor Services Representative (IL)</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Interactive Brokers Group is expanding its Professional Services department at our main call center in Chicago, IL. We are searching for candidates with prior experience in the financial services industry, with interpersonal, communication and technology skills that are FINRA registered. Our aim is to build and maintain long-term customer relationships with independent financial advisors and their clients as we continue to expand our global market access, sophisticated trading tools and product offerings. The Financial Advisor Services Representative will provide support which will encompass all facets of the client experience at IB, including account application assistance, funding support and trade inquiries as well as the configuration and operation of our trading platform, the Trader Workstation. Responsibilities Act as liaison to Interactive Broker's top-tier clients, with a focus on financial advisors, striving to provide solutions to inquiries while complying with all policies, practices and procedures. Problem management with focus on wide scale service issues. Core competences include: handling trade-related issues, trade and margin analysis, account management and funding, product (cash market, equities and derivatives) and exchange knowledge (global), technical services, securities regulations. Internal coordinator to various departments such as technical operations and programming, analyzing and escalating issues appropriately. Special projects including the development of new customer service technologies, assessments of existing systems, review and audit projects, etc. Qualifications Education : Bachelor's degree in Finance, Economics, Business Administration or other related field, or equivalent work experience. The candidate must possess general market knowledge in futures, options, and the equities markets. Experience : 3 years financial industry experience preferred with client services background required Skills : Strong interpersonal and written communication skills. Must demonstrate excellent analytical and problem resolution skills. Computer Skills : Working knowledge of PC technologies, including Microsoft Word, Excel, Databases. Programming and/or UNIX experience a plus. Registrations : FINRA Series 7. Series 55, 63 desirable. Multi-language skills a plus.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977059</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Operations| Financial Advisor Services Representative (IL)</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Financial Advisor Services Representative (IL)</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Chicago, IL, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Chicago</city>
      <state>IL</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-CT-Greenwich-Security_System%E2%80%99s_Programmer.id01977062?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>47400f3beb0f420cfa2df28af0e384a5</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Security System’s Programmer</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Responsibilities The Security System's Programmer will be responsible for: Vulnerability assessments, management, report preparation The Security System's Programmer will be responsible for: Monitoring and responding to security alerts Software initiative Internal penetration testing, Verifying risk factors Assisting with prioritizing of remediation steps and coordinating remediation steps with other technology teams Building and extending IT security infrastructure and automation of related tasks Qualifications Minimum of Bachelor's degree in a technology related field 5+ years of IT experience plus 3+ years of IT security experience plus 2+ years of Linux experience plus 2+ years of C programming or equivalent skill level (at least intermediate) 2+ years of hands on experience with a scripting language Python, Perl, Shell etc. 2+ years of hands on experience working with IP networks, firewalls and routing methodology. Excellent analytical and problem-solving skills with a Self-discipline Security-focused mindset</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977062</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Information Technology| Security System’s Programmer</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Security System’s Programmer</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Greenwich, CT, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Greenwich</city>
      <state>CT</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-DC-Washington_DC-RIA_Compliance_Professional.id01984390?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>e7495e3ef4e876a2944a08483d3629ef</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>RIA Compliance Professional</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. IB Group has recently formed a new company, Greenwich Advisor Compliance Services ("Greenwich Compliance"), that offers registration and compliance services to investment advisors who wish to use the Interactive Brokers platform. IB Group and its Greenwich Compliance subsidiary are growing rapidly. We are looking to expand our Greenwich Compliance team by adding a motivated and talented compliance professional familiar with the compliance obligations of SEC- and state-registered investment advisors, the Investment Advisers Act of 1940 and similar state statutes. Responsibilities Responding to registration and compliance questions from current and potential investment advisors. Working with advisors to prepare their SEC and state registration filings, including Form ADV filings. Working with advisors to draft their compliance manuals, codes of ethics, and other written policies and procedures. Interacting with the SEC, state regulatory agencies and other regulatory bodies in connection with efforts to get investment advisors registered. Drafting various written materials for use by advisors to help them meet their compliance obligations and/or respond to regulatory inquiries. Drafting web content and periodic releases on compliance issues of interest to investment advisors. Qualifications Ideal candidate should possess at least two years of work experience but no more than 5 years of experience. Candidates with experience related to investment management compliance issues at a regulator, industry association, compliance firm, an investment advisory firm, or another broker-dealer or FCM are preferred. Solid academic background. High degree of comfort and fluency with computers and technology, and understanding of how technology is applied to business and regulatory problems. Outstanding oral and written communication skills. Ability to develop compliance solutions that satisfy relevant regulations while executing sound business judgment. Ability to proactively engage a diverse group of clients. Ability to work in a small-team environment and independently and to multi-task with minimal supervision.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01984390</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Compliance/Legal| RIA Compliance Professional</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>RIA Compliance Professional</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Washington D.C., DC, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Washington D.C.</city>
      <state>DC</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-TX-Austin-LATINO_MARKET_MANAGER.id02247174?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>2897272e5d0dd323b9696b585de8df01</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>LATINO MARKET MANAGER</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>New York Life Insurance Company ("New York Life" or "the company") is the largest mutual life insurance company in the United States*. Founded in 1845, New York Life is headquartered in New York City, maintains offices in all fifty states, and owns Seguros Monterrey New York Life in Mexico. New York Life is one of the most financially strong and highly capitalized insurers in the business. The company reported 2016 operating earnings of $1.954 billion. Total assets under management at year end 2016, with affiliates, totaled $538 billion. As of year-end 2016, New York Life's surplus was $23.336 billion**. New York Life holds the highest possible financial strength ratings currently awarded to any life insurer from all four of the major ratings agencies: A.M. Best, A++; Fitch AAA; Moody's Aaa; Standard &amp; Poor's AA+. (Source: Individual Third Party Ratings Report as of 8/17/16). Financial strength, integrity and humanity-the values upon which New York Life was founded-have guided the company's decisions and actions for over 170 years. General Profile: The Senior Associate, Bilingual Recruiting &amp; Marketing individual responsibility is to support the Latino Market sales &amp; recruiting strategy. The Senior Associate role is to help build an incremental unit of successful Latino Market New York Life Agents that contribute substantially to the overall growth of the General Office and the Latino Market. The Senior Associate will engage the Latino community to drive sales and recruiting growth objectives. Responsibilities include: • Work with local management and the Home Office to build the Latino Market recruiting and marketing plans. • Coordinating Home Office Recruiting and Marketing programs within the General Office. • Working with Latino business, community, and professional organizations in all surrounding municipalities. One must be an active participant to leverage opportunities to market to their constituents. • Identifying and executing all Latino market community affairs events where the General Office can actively participate for sales and recruiting lead generation. • Manage local Latino recruiting &amp; marketing event schedule and communications. • Assist the Latino Market Unit (Home Office) to implement local corporate and agent co-op branding initiatives to communicate a uniform message locally, and effectively leverage for sales and recruiting results. • Disseminate Latino marketing materials for new agents i.e. Welcome Kit, Relationship Marketing System Materials (RMS), New Agent Brochures, etc. Work with new agents to enroll them in fast start initiatives, Company sponsored programs, and specific Latino marketing activities. Functional Knowledge: • Should have at least 5 years of professional business experience and/or a minimum of 2 years insurance sales experience or executive recruiting experience • Excellent written and oral communication skills • Must have an indepth understanding of the Latino culture and community • Bilingual (English/Spanish) required, verbal and written • Above average technical skills (MS Word, Excel and PowerPoint) • Must be familiar with the areas surrounding the General Office and have existing relationships with local Latino community-based, business, and professional organizations and companies • Strong organizational skills, detail oriented • Insurance Field sales experience, a plus Decision Making / Nature of Impact: This individual will have day-to-day decision-making authority, and will present recommendations to the CVP and Managing Partner for all strategic Latino Market recruiting initiatives for the office. Communication Requirements: The Senior Associate will communicate regularly with the CVP - Latino Field Market Managers, Managing Partners, Development Managers, Recruiters, and the Latino Market Unit in Westchester, NY. EOE M/F/D/V If you have difficulty using or interacting with any portions of this Web site due to incompatibility with an Assistive Technology, if you need the information in an alternative format, or if you have suggestions on how we can make this site more accessible, please contact us at: (212) 576-5811. * Based on revenue as reported by "Fortune 500, ranked within Industries, Insurance: Life, Health (Mutual)," Fortune Magazine, June 17, 2016. See http://fortune.com/fortune500/ for methodology. ** Total surplus, which includes the Asset Valuation Reserve, is one of the key indicators of the company's long-term financial strength and stability and is presented on a consolidated basis of the company. 1. Operating earnings is the key measure use by management to track Company's profitability from ongoing operations and underlying profitability of the business. This indicator is based on generally accepted accounting principles in the US (GAAP), with certain adjustments Company believes to be appropriate as a measurement approach (non GAAP), primarily the removal of gains or losses on investments and related adjustments. 2. Assets under management represent Consolidated Domestic and International insurance Company Statutory assets (cash and invested assets and separate account assets) and third party assets principally managed by New York Life Investment management Holdings LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of New York Life Insurance Company. SF-MC1 SF:EF-MC1</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  New York Life Insurance</company>
      <jobid>02247174</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Sales &amp; Marketing| LATINO MARKET MANAGER</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>LATINO MARKET MANAGER</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Austin, TX, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Austin</city>
      <state>TX</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-CT-Greenwich-Junior_Quality_Assurance_Engineer.id02163521?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>70a5e28f4f146f1abbd9825bda1b3c07</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Junior Quality Assurance Engineer</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Interactive Brokers is seeking a Quality Assurance Engineer for our Web Development Group to develop, document and maintain test cases for our client facing systems. Responsibilities The successful candidate must be proficient with manually testing client facing systems and be able to write scripts for automated functional and regression testing of these applications. The QA process will include development of test cases, test plans and test scripts. The candidate must be highly analytical and adept at solving complex problems. Qualifications BS in Computer Science, Engineering or Mathematics Internship as a quality assurance analyst or 1 year of working experience Experience with Selenium or Java Exposure to UNIX/Linux, SQL, JUnit Working understanding of HTML and JavaScript Problem solver, attention to details, fast learner Self-motivated and directed</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>02163521</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Information Technology| Junior Quality Assurance Engineer</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Junior Quality Assurance Engineer</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Greenwich, CT, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Greenwich</city>
      <state>CT</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-NY-New_York-VP_Market_Risk_Implementation.id02301530?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>fe013110f34b2ab8b27fa663e37f890b</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>VP Market Risk Implementation</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>You will be responsible for implementing the next generation market risk analytics platform for the bank. Additionally, you will integrate pricing models and work on the analytics delivery for market risk calculations.    The team is comprised of PhD and Masters level individuals with backgrounds in Physics, Statistics, Applied Mathematics, and Computer Science. The ideal candidate comes from a background in risk management, understands the stochastic process and statistics, and is proficient technically in C++ or Python. They are guided by logic and see themselves as a natural problem solver. Responsibilities Implement the bank's next generation market risk analytics platform Integrate pricing models Work on the analytics delivery for market risk calculations Requirements Expertise in C++ and/or Python, including experience with numpy, scipy and/or pandas Expertise in data structures, standard algorithms and OO design. Strong design skills and implementation skills Strong analytical and problem solving abilities. Probability theory, financial math or stochastic calculus is a plus Development using multi threading, GPU, MPI, grid, or other HPC technologies  is a plus  </jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Non-disclosed</company>
      <jobid>02301530</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Risk Management| VP Market Risk Implementation</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>VP Market Risk Implementation</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  New York, NY, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  New York</city>
      <state>NY</state>
      <payrate>140000-185000</payrate>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-NY-New_York-Senior_Associate_Finance_Project_Manager.id02227802?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>f664337e3bc2f3c6b4f6cdee74b7a64d</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Senior Associate, Finance Project Manager</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>New York Life Insurance Company ("New York Life" or "the company") is the largest mutual life insurance company in the United States*. Founded in 1845, New York Life is headquartered in New York City, maintains offices in all fifty states, and owns Seguros Monterrey New York Life in Mexico. New York Life is one of the most financially strong and highly capitalized insurers in the business. The company reported 2016 operating earnings of $1.954 billion. Total assets under management at year end 2016, with affiliates, totaled $538 billion. As of year-end 2016, New York Life's surplus was $23.336 billion**. New York Life holds the highest possible financial strength ratings currently awarded to any life insurer from all four of the major ratings agencies: A.M. Best, A++; Fitch AAA; Moody's Aaa; Standard &amp; Poor's AA+. (Source: Individual Third Party Ratings Report as of 8/17/16). Financial strength, integrity and humanity-the values upon which New York Life was founded-have guided the company's decisions and actions for over 170 years. Overview The portfolio lead is responsible for managing the day to day execution of projects within the Finance Portfolio. As a project manager, this role will be tasked with establishing a project plan and managing delivery. This role will drive the implementation of standard project/program/portfolio standards such as project tracking, risk/issue management, and metrics and status reporting. Responsibilities Oversee and manage projects within the Finance portfolio end to end Identify project risks/issues and communicate to Stakeholders Liaise with project stakeholders to actively manage scope, timeline and budget Ensure compliance against Project Management standards Support Business Case development as necessary Assist in the continuous improvement of Finance processes Qualifications Bachelor's Degree 5+ years of Project Management experience Experience and familiarity with Finance and Accounting principles Excellent written and verbal communication skills Ability to execute strategies and track and measure results Ability to clearly communicate expectations Ability to work effectively and achieve results across all involved functional areas/parties SF:LI-JL1 SF:EF-JL1 EOE M/F/D/V If you have difficulty using or interacting with any portions of this Web site due to incompatibility with an Assistive Technology, if you need the information in an alternative format, or if you have suggestions on how we can make this site more accessible, please contact us at: (212) 576-5811. * Based on revenue as reported by "Fortune 500, ranked within Industries, Insurance: Life, Health (Mutual)," Fortune Magazine, June 17, 2016. See http://fortune.com/fortune500/ for methodology. ** Total surplus, which includes the Asset Valuation Reserve, is one of the key indicators of the company's long-term financial strength and stability and is presented on a consolidated basis of the company. 1. Operating earnings is the key measure use by management to track Company's profitability from ongoing operations and underlying profitability of the business. This indicator is based on generally accepted accounting principles in the US (GAAP), with certain adjustments Company believes to be appropriate as a measurement approach (non GAAP), primarily the removal of gains or losses on investments and related adjustments. 2. Assets under management represent Consolidated Domestic and International insurance Company Statutory assets (cash and invested assets and separate account assets) and third party assets principally managed by New York Life Investment management Holdings LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of New York Life Insurance Company.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  New York Life Insurance</company>
      <jobid>02227802</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Accounting &amp; Finance| Senior Associate, Finance Project Manager</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Senior Associate, Finance Project Manager</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  New York, NY, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  New York</city>
      <state>NY</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-IL-Chicago-Customer_Service_Representative_-_Trade_Issues.id02023537?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>b7655ec5c26e1ae68e9aed878bd24bd1</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Customer Service Representative - Trade Issues</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Interactive Brokers Group is expanding its Trading Issues Department at our main retail call center in Chicago, IL. We are searching for experienced candidates with a prior background in the financial services industry, that are FINRA registered for the position of Customer Service Representative . The Trade Issues Customer Service Representative is accountable for providing a high level of client service to IB's existing retail and institutional clients. Our aim is thoroughly investigate trade inquiries, in particular, but also covers various other areas under the general customer service umbrella. [i] Figures as of December 31, 2015. Information on the company can be found at www.interactivebrokers.com Responsibilities Problem management with focus on wide scale service issues. Core competencies include, but are not limited to: trade and margin analysis, a wide range of products (cash market and derivatives) and global exchanges, order types, and transmission and execution inquiries. The candidate must possess general market knowledge in futures, options, and the equities markets. Previous customer service experience in a financial services or banking operations environment required. Investigate customer inquiries regarding trade-related issues (e.g., executions, position liquidations, order trigger conditions, trade cancellation requests, product availability &amp; attributes, order types and routing logic etc.) Assistance with trading platform operation and features; analyze and test existing systems and procedures in order to recommend and assist in the implementation enhancements Respond to inquiries, concerns and complaints from existing and prospective customers via telephone, e-mail, and on-line chat to achieve a solution that is mutually satisfactory while complying with policies, practices and procedures Must demonstrate excellent troubleshooting and problem resolution skills required to bring problems quickly to a resolution. Order status, settlement, exercise &amp; assignment, expiration processing, and corporate actions Qualifications Experience: 2 years financial industry experience with trading or brokerage services preferred; but will consider recent college graduate Education: Bachelor's degree in Finance, Economics, Business Administration or other related field Certification: Registrations: FINRA Series 7, 63 Computer: Strong PC technologies proficiency preferred; Microsoft Word &amp; Excel Strong quantitative analytical skills Excellent oral/written communication skills required</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>02023537</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Operations| Customer Service Representative - Trade Issues</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Customer Service Representative - Trade Issues</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Chicago, IL, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Chicago</city>
      <state>IL</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-IL-Chicago-Client_Service_Representative_-_Tax_ReportingRetirement.id01977065?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>92132c5545f75f13d891b5fcbf3d8ee6</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Client Service Representative - Tax Reporting/Retirement</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. The ideal candidate will have a background in financial markets, have experience in stocks and options. Full understanding of futures, and foreign exchange spot markets. *We thank all applicants, however due to the high volume of responses only those selected for the selection process will be contacted. Responsibilities Handle escalated Tax and IRA service issues. The inquiries typically encompass information reporting, filing and compliance for US, Canadian and other foreign accounts. Areas of concentration include the following: IRS TIN verification and back up withholding issues W-8 recertification for non-US taxpayers Year-end tax reports and forms, including the IRS Worksheets IRA contributions and distributions IRA beneficiary options Dividend classifications and treaty rates Wash sale calculations FATCA Compliance Respond to retail and professional client inquiries via inbound calls, email and on-line chat. Demonstrate knowledge of securities regulations. Coordinate activities with local and international Customer Service divisions, as well as third-party agencies. Resolve routine and complex client service issues in a thorough and expeditious manner. Perform tax and IRA related account maintenance transactions, including IRA transfers, IRA distributions, cost basis updates, and dividend tax classifications. Research, verify, and facilitate corrected IRS tax forms for proper reporting of client transactions. Maintain current knowledge of trends and developments impacting retirement accounts, including IRS regulations. Qualifications Experience: 2 years in trading or brokerage services, but will consider recent college graduate. Education: University degree (Bachelors) required Computer: Strong IT proficiency preferred Good quantitative/analytical skills Excellent oral/written communication skills required Knowledge of retirement accounts and tax considerations a plus. Strong research, communication and writing skills are required</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977065</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Operations| Client Service Representative - Tax Reporting/Retirement</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Client Service Representative - Tax Reporting/Retirement</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Chicago, IL, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Chicago</city>
      <state>IL</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-CT-Greenwich-Software_Engineer.id02301514?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>7fb2caaaf5cfd24bab286e681398fba3</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Software Engineer</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Join a team responsible for automating all aspects of securities lending and borrowing. This is a great opportunity to work on applications which add directly to the company's bottom line and learn about the underlying business. Interactive Brokers (NASDAQ: IBKR) is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 26 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Responsibilities The successful candidate must take ownership of assigned projects and all phases of the software lifecycle, while working in a fast paced agile environment. Daily tasks will include but are not limited to: Develop backend services and algorithms for new features. Optimize, improve, and support existing algorithms and code base. Develop multi-tier JEE and batch applications. Write well designed, tested and clean code. Qualifications • Bachelors or MS in Computer Science, Engineering, Mathematics or Physical Sciences • 1-10 years of Java experience • Strong knowledge of object oriented concepts &amp; multi-tier applications • Strong understanding of DBMS concepts (Oracle platform is a plus) • Hands on expertise in server side programming in Java/C++ J2EE experience • Knowledge of financial instruments is a plus</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>02301514</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Information Technology| Software Engineer</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Software Engineer</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Greenwich, CT, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Greenwich</city>
      <state>CT</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-CT-Greenwich-Senior_Compliance_Analyst.id01977043?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>c7cbfe72face3620de89a532780c316a</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Senior Compliance Analyst</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Timber Hill is a market maker in equity options, futures and index products around the world. Timber Hill was founded on the principle that a computerized trading system that could process pricing and integrated risk exposure information quickly would allow the firm to profitably make markets in many different listed financial instruments simultaneously. The Company's market making is focused on capturing bid/offer spreads in the course of providing liquidity in listed financial instruments. Timber Hill has revolutionized trading in exchange-traded equity options and equity-index options and futures through the use of technology to automate and integrate trading and risk management functions. Interactive Brokers LLC is an SEC-registered broker-dealer and a CFTC-registered futures commission merchant, as well as a member of FINRA and the NFA. Our legal and compliance department is growing and we are looking for high quality talent. [i] Figures as of December 31 , 2015. Information on the company can be found at: www.interactivebrokers.com Responsibilities The Senior Compliance Analyst position requires familiarity with SEC, FINRA, CFTC and NFA rules and regulations and appropriate experience at a regulatory agency, exchange, broker-dealer or FCM. Review and principal approval of advertisements, marketing materials and webinars written by IB staff and materials posted by third-party service providers on Interactive's Investors' Marketplace. Handling regulatory inquiries from the SEC, FINRA, CFTC, and NFA concerning securities, commodities and derivatives trading and compliance issues. Researching, interpreting and advising the firm regarding compliance with laws, regulations and guidance applicable to broker-dealers and futures commission merchants. Meeting with and responding to the FINRA and NFA regulators during audits of the firm. Filing of required communications for regulatory approval Review of daily and weekly surveillance reports. Drafting and implementing firm policies and written supervisory procedures. Developing and implementing remedial action plans in response to internal and external audit findings. Qualifications 5 years' experience with the SEC, FINRA, CFTC, NFA, an exchange or another broker-dealer or FCM. Appropriately registered compliance officer (i.e., at least a Series 24 and/or Series 3 and Series 4 registration). Solid academic background with strong quantitative/analytical skills. Experience with FINRA and NFA rules concerning broker-dealer and FCM communications with the public, including the requirements for filing communications for regulatory approval would be strongly preferred. Prior experience in highly automated environment and/or high degree of comfort and fluency with computers and technology, and understanding of how technology is applied to business and regulatory issues. Outstanding oral and written communication skills. Ability to develop compliance solutions that satisfy relevant regulations while executing sound business judgment. Ability to work in a small-team environment and to work independently and to multi-task with minimal supervision.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977043</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Compliance/Legal| Senior Compliance Analyst</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Senior Compliance Analyst</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Greenwich, CT, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Greenwich</city>
      <state>CT</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-CT-Greenwich-Senior_Software_Engineer_-_Java_Backend.id01977041?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>17cb66d2dfc04cca31610e386ecf6aba</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Senior Software Engineer - Java Backend</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Responsibilities Brokerage platform development -- front and/or back-end, depending on experience. Back end: Core Java. Data model and transport layers. Multithreaded/high throughput. XML. Work on one of the core brokerage processes that deals with user authentication to access trading, account management and other customer applications. Adding new features and interfaces that deal with user authentication. Work on expanding second factor authentication offering. Qualifications Bachelor's in EE, CS, Math, Physics or similar (Masters/PhD a plus). Technically oriented, proactive, and enthusiastic, with extreme attention to detail. 5+ years' Java experience. Knowledge of core Java. Working with Database development SQL and PL/SQL is a plus. English written/verbal communication skills. Mobile software development a plus. [1] Figures as of September 30, 2016. Information on the company can be found at: www.interactivebrokers.com</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977041</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Information Technology| Senior Software Engineer - Java Backend</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Senior Software Engineer - Java Backend</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Greenwich, CT, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Greenwich</city>
      <state>CT</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-CT-Greenwich-Mandarin_Web_and_Video_Specialist.id02301515?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>3aa91f7351745ce03f3f87d1acf8d593</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Mandarin Web and Video Specialist</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers Group, Inc. (NASDAQ:IBKR) is seeking a web and video production specialist fluent in both Mandarin and English to work in our fast-paced, dynamic, and demanding environment marketing team at our Greenwich, Connecticut location. The candidate will be expected to provide quality assurance to our Chinese website, assist Chinese language related marketing strategies, and produce educational video content in Chinese. The candidate must be a team player, creative, and willing to take new challenges and assignments. Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 26 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Responsibilities Produce market commentary suitable for Chinese readers. Select applicable market analysis articles and provide translation for Chinese specific marketing campaigns; Chinese social media management, including daily posting and monthly data analysis; Produce Chinese short videos, including scrip preparation, filming, editing and publishing; Provide quality control to IB's Chinese website to ensure the website structure and content are up to date; Translate Chinese marketing materials and documentation; Conduct media research as needed; Coordinating ad hoc projects if required. Qualifications Bachelor's degree 2-5 years working experience Good knowledge of financial markets and financial terminologies Technical savvy Proficient in MS Office Bilingual proficiency in English and Chinese Strong written communication skills Team player Basic HTML knowledge Knowledge of Camtasia and Flare/Lingo is a plus</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>02301515</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Sales &amp; Marketing| Mandarin Web and Video Specialist</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Mandarin Web and Video Specialist</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Greenwich, CT, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Greenwich</city>
      <state>CT</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-NC-Charlotte-Risk_and_Regulatory_-_Process_Improvement_%E2%80%93Consultant_Multiple_levels.id01991600?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>7b9246634fbbaf02bfc705ec5b9acc23</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Risk and Regulatory - Process Improvement –Consultant (Multiple levels)</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>About Sia Partners: Sia Partners is a unique management consulting firm composed of 850+ passionate consultants who drive business changes among our customers. Through unparalleled industry expertise, we deliver superior value and tangible results to our clients in over 21 sectors and service teams. Financial institutions has drastically changed over the last decade and further revolutions are yet to come.  Regulatory constraints have driven most of these transformations, but the disruptive revolution is much more complex and cannot be limited to the latter. Business models must be adapted within each business line and operating models must take into account industrial partnership, outsourcing or strategic alliances.   Sia Partners assists its clients in coping with these transformations in order to improve their competitive advantages, flexibility productivity and profitability: strategic deployment, financial performance, business process optimization, digitalization, risk and regulatory adherence.  Sia Partners is hiring in Charlotte, NC! Thanks to Sia Partners’ international footprint, the Financial Services practice is strategically located in all major financial and energy hubs (New York, Charlotte, UK, Europe, and Asia Pacific) and our integrated model allows teams from different countries to easily partner, when appropriate. Job description Responsibilities: Undertake various client engagements and ensure consistent delivery of superior client service; this includes leading and assuming responsibility for high quality programs, initiatives, deliverables while respecting established time frames and budget. Participate in assessment and delivery of projects that will include: Risk and regulatory adherence Process improvement Business transformation Qualifications: 3-8 years of management consulting or other relevant domain knowledge and experience in financial services Bachelors’ Degree in Business Administration, Accounting, Finance, Economics, or other business related fields Advanced attention to detail Excellent written and verbal communications skills Excellent interpersonal and teamwork skills Analytical and quantitative problem solving skills Ability to adapt rapidly, and work on a range of different business areas within a challenging environment and tight deadlines  </jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Sia Partners</company>
      <jobid>01991600</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Accounting &amp; Finance| Risk and Regulatory - Process Improvement –Consultant (Multiple levels)</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Risk and Regulatory - Process Improvement –Consultant (Multiple levels)</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Charlotte, NC, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Charlotte</city>
      <state>NC</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-FL-Miami-SENIOR_ASSOCIATE_Sales_and_Retention_Manager.id02268839?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>ae9e11ebe026bcc3ecfec33af50830d6</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>SENIOR ASSOCIATE, Sales and Retention Manager</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>New York Life Insurance Company ("New York Life" or "the company") is the largest mutual life insurance company in the United States*. Founded in 1845, New York Life is headquartered in New York City, maintains offices in all fifty states, and owns Seguros Monterrey New York Life in Mexico. New York Life is one of the most financially strong and highly capitalized insurers in the business. The company reported 2016 operating earnings of $1.954 billion. Total assets under management at year end 2016, with affiliates, totaled $538 billion. As of year-end 2016, New York Life's surplus was $23.336 billion**. New York Life holds the highest possible financial strength ratings currently awarded to any life insurer from all four of the major ratings agencies: A.M. Best, A++; Fitch AAA; Moody's Aaa; Standard &amp; Poor's AA+. (Source: Individual Third Party Ratings Report as of 8/17/16). Financial strength, integrity and humanity-the values upon which New York Life was founded-have guided the company's decisions and actions for over 170 years. General Profile The Senior Associate of Sales Support and Retention is responsible for the development and implementation of the Latino Market Agent support plan in the areas of sales, Agent retention, manpower or productivity, and market development activities in the assigned geographical territory/Zone. The Senior Associate will work closely with the Latino Market Zone Manager and the business area's Analysis and Reporting team to analyze key indicators, identify needs, develop and implement action plans and activities designed to drive sales and learning activities in the Field with Agents and Managers in the assigned territory. Specifically, the Senior Associate will be responsible for driving retention, manpower, and productivity among all Agents in the Latino Market, with a focus on New Organization Agents or those in their first three years in the business. The Senior Associate will facilitate in language and bilingual training, development, and sales activities in specific Focus Offices and with Agents on an individual basis. Major responsibilities Partner with Zone Manager and General Office Development teams to build agent retention and manpower support plans as well as to implement Latino Market Agent orientation, skill builders, prospecting activities, training, and study groups or other development and sales programs. Conduct assessment of the Latino Market Agents in target General Offices to identify target agents and develop tactics to increase agent production: Life Case Rate, Life Commissions, Retention, Manpower. Conduct Hispanic Market sales campaigns such as canvassing activities, phone clinics, business blitz campaigns, sales seminars, and other local sponsorship opportunities. Conduct individual Agent meetings to review production opportunities, sales ideas, activity, and accountability, develop individual plans and follow up. Qualifications Bachelor's degree required/equivalent business experience. Life and Health licenses are required, 6 and 63 a plus. Minimum of 2 - 4 years of relevant experience. One or more of the following is required: Sales, Insurance, Marketing, Sales Management, Sales Coaching experience. Life insurance sales experience is a must, having demonstrated success as an individual producer, along with thorough knowledge of New York Life sales systems, products namely Life Insurance, Annuities, and New York Life's Financial Needs Analysis approach. Must possess strong leadership qualities, excellent verbal and written communication skills with influencing others, and strong ability to problem solve, think critically and collaborate cross functionally. EOE M/F/D/V If you have difficulty using or interacting with any portions of this Web site due to incompatibility with an Assistive Technology, if you need the information in an alternative format, or if you have suggestions on how we can make this site more accessible, please contact us at: (212) 576-5811. * Based on revenue as reported by "Fortune 500, ranked within Industries, Insurance: Life, Health (Mutual)," Fortune Magazine, June 17, 2016. See http://fortune.com/fortune500/ for methodology. ** Total surplus, which includes the Asset Valuation Reserve, is one of the key indicators of the company's long-term financial strength and stability and is presented on a consolidated basis of the company. 1. Operating earnings is the key measure use by management to track Company's profitability from ongoing operations and underlying profitability of the business. This indicator is based on generally accepted accounting principles in the US (GAAP), with certain adjustments Company believes to be appropriate as a measurement approach (non GAAP), primarily the removal of gains or losses on investments and related adjustments. 2. Assets under management represent Consolidated Domestic and International insurance Company Statutory assets (cash and invested assets and separate account assets) and third party assets principally managed by New York Life Investment management Holdings LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of New York Life Insurance Company. SF:LI-MC1 SF:EF-MC1</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  New York Life Insurance</company>
      <jobid>02268839</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Sales &amp; Marketing| SENIOR ASSOCIATE, Sales and Retention Manager</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>SENIOR ASSOCIATE, Sales and Retention Manager</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Miami, FL, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Miami</city>
      <state>FL</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-KS-Wichita-ASSOCIATE_Sales_Development_Manager.id02227804?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>2e3051aaf170b1c4ffd6fb499fb71459</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>ASSOCIATE, Sales Development Manager</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>New York Life Insurance Company ("New York Life" or "the company") is the largest mutual life insurance company in the United States*. Founded in 1845, New York Life is headquartered in New York City, maintains offices in all fifty states, and owns Seguros Monterrey New York Life in Mexico. New York Life is one of the most financially strong and highly capitalized insurers in the business. The company reported 2016 operating earnings of $1.954 billion. Total assets under management at year end 2016, with affiliates, totaled $538 billion. As of year-end 2016, New York Life's surplus was $23.336 billion**. New York Life holds the highest possible financial strength ratings currently awarded to any life insurer from all four of the major ratings agencies: A.M. Best, A++; Fitch AAA; Moody's Aaa; Standard &amp; Poor's AA+. (Source: Individual Third Party Ratings Report as of 8/17/16). Financial strength, integrity and humanity-the values upon which New York Life was founded-have guided the company's decisions and actions for over 170 years. Duties and responsibilitiess of the Associate Development Manager for the Kansas GO: Ensure the complete and proper implementation of the NYLIC University Curriculum and systems. This includes the preparation for the conducting of Group and drill, Individual Instruction and Drill, and Field Observation and Demonstration. Work with the Managing Partner to ensure the complete and proper implementation of the GOLD System in the General Office. This includes conducting Performance Review and Planning sessions with agents, conducting Agent Development Planning meetings with Partners and Managing Partners, assisting with Monthly Planning Meetings, and Annual Planning Meetings. Sales promotion. Assisting in the communication to agents of General Office, Zone and Home Office promotions. Assisting agents with case preparation and in the field conducting Field Observation and Demonstration as well as assisting in presenting and closing sales. Learning the GOLD System and how to properly implement the GOLD Systems in the General Office. Learning the NYLIC University Systems, company resources, and how to properly implement them in the General Office. Learning the skills necessary to develop agents; classroom facilitation skills, etc. Develop a working knowledge of NYLIC Products. Qualifications: Valid State Life and Health Licenses FINRA Registrations, Series 6, 63 FINRA Series 26 registration within 120 days Good written and oral communication skills Functional Knowledge: Has general understanding of NYL's businesses and uses this understanding to accomplish own work. Problem Solving: Solves problems in straightforward situations; analyzes possible solutions using education and/or equivalent experience, judgment and precedents. Decision Making/Nature of Impact: Makes recommendations to the Zone Training Officer and the Managing Partner concerning General Office training events and initiatives. Communication Requirements: Summarizes and explains information to others. EOE M/F/D/V If you have difficulty using or interacting with any portions of this Web site due to incompatibility with an Assistive Technology, if you need the information in an alternative format, or if you have suggestions on how we can make this site more accessible, please contact us at: (212) 576-5811. * Based on revenue as reported by "Fortune 500, ranked within Industries, Insurance: Life, Health (Mutual)," Fortune Magazine, June 17, 2016. See http://fortune.com/fortune500/ for methodology. ** Total surplus, which includes the Asset Valuation Reserve, is one of the key indicators of the company's long-term financial strength and stability and is presented on a consolidated basis of the company. 1. Operating earnings is the key measure use by management to track Company's profitability from ongoing operations and underlying profitability of the business. This indicator is based on generally accepted accounting principles in the US (GAAP), with certain adjustments Company believes to be appropriate as a measurement approach (non GAAP), primarily the removal of gains or losses on investments and related adjustments. 2. Assets under management represent Consolidated Domestic and International insurance Company Statutory assets (cash and invested assets and separate account assets) and third party assets principally managed by New York Life Investment management Holdings LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of New York Life Insurance Company.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  New York Life Insurance</company>
      <jobid>02227804</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Sales &amp; Marketing| ASSOCIATE, Sales Development Manager</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>ASSOCIATE, Sales Development Manager</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Wichita, KS, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Wichita</city>
      <state>KS</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-CT-Greenwich-Technical_Assistance_Center_Representative.id01977054?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>3e67adcb85dd38e2138b710b37835d15</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Technical Assistance Center Representative</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. The Technical Assistance team is focused on ensuring a solid user experience through the responsive support of our trading software. As a member of the technical assistance team, you will assist customers with inquiries pertaining to all of our software products and become an expert with IB's trading software and gain a deep understanding of the products we offer. You have the networking and programming knowledge to troubleshoot issues that pertain to our trading client programs. The successful candidate will be intellectual and analytical, and are able to recognize, test, and escalate new bugs within our software. [i] Figures as of September 30, 2016. Information on the company can be found at: www.interactivebrokers.com Responsibilities Be a liaison between internal teams and customers to ensure a prompt and effective resolution of bugs and issues. Assist a diverse range of domestic and international customers with installing, configuring, and troubleshooting our trading software and our website. Escalate issues to software developers and server operators. Address inquiries and issues regarding IB's two-factor secure login system. Qualifications Minimum Qualifications: 4 year college degree Prior experience in a customer-facing role Excellent written and verbal communication skills Experience troubleshooting networking or software related issues Preferred Qualifications: 4 year degree in a STEM field 2 years in a network or software support role, primarily in a call-center or realtime support environment Experience with Unix and basic Unix commands Financial services industry related experience and knowledge of common financial products Mandarin, Spanish or Russian language skills a plus</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977054</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Operations| Technical Assistance Center Representative</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Technical Assistance Center Representative</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Greenwich, CT, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Greenwich</city>
      <state>CT</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-NY-White_Plains-SENIOR_ASSOCIATE_Sales_and_Retention_Manager.id02216273?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>b9e3e72060526fcc3ae38fb8bb0ec28c</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>SENIOR ASSOCIATE, Sales and Retention Manager</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>New York Life Insurance Company ("New York Life" or "the company") is the largest mutual life insurance company in the United States*. Founded in 1845, New York Life is headquartered in New York City, maintains offices in all fifty states, and owns Seguros Monterrey New York Life in Mexico. New York Life is one of the most financially strong and highly capitalized insurers in the business. The company reported 2016 operating earnings of $1.954 billion. Total assets under management at year end 2016, with affiliates, totaled $538 billion. As of year-end 2016, New York Life's surplus was $23.336 billion**. New York Life holds the highest possible financial strength ratings currently awarded to any life insurer from all four of the major ratings agencies: A.M. Best, A++; Fitch AAA; Moody's Aaa; Standard &amp; Poor's AA+. (Source: Individual Third Party Ratings Report as of 8/17/16). Financial strength, integrity and humanity-the values upon which New York Life was founded-have guided the company's decisions and actions for over 170 years. General Profile: The Senior Associate, Sales and Retention Manager is responsible for the development and implementation of the Latino Market Agent support plan in the areas of sales, Agent retention, manpower or productivity, and market development activities in the assigned geographical territory/Zone. The Senior Associate will work closely with the Latino Market Zone Manager and the business area's Analysis and Reporting team to analyze key indicators, identify needs, develop and implement action plans and activities designed to drive sales and learning activities in the Field with Agents and Managers in the assigned territory. Specifically, the Senior Associate will be responsible for driving retention, manpower, and productivity among all Agents in the Latino Market, with a focus on New Organization Agents or those in their first three years in the business. The Senior Associate will facilitate in language and bilingual training, development, and sales activities in specific Focus Offices and with Agents on an individual basis. Major responsibilities: • Partner with Zone Manager and General Office Development teams to build agent retention and manpower support plans as well as to implement Latino Market Agent orientation, skill builders, prospecting activities, training, and study groups or other development and sales programs. • Conduct assessment of the Latino Market Agents in target General Offices to identify target agents and develop tactics to increase agent production: Life Case Rate, Life Commissions, Retention, Manpower. • Conduct Hispanic Market sales campaigns such as canvassing activities, phone clinics, business blitz campaigns, sales seminars, and other local sponsorship opportunities. • Conduct individual Agent meetings to review production opportunities, sales ideas, activity, and accountability, develop individual plans and follow up. Qualifications: • Bachelors degree required/equivalent business experience. • Life and Health licenses are required, 6 and 63 a plus. • Minimum 2-4 years of relevant experience. • One or more of the following is required: Sales, Insurance, Marketing, Sales Management, Sales Coaching experience. • Life insurance sales experience is a must, having demonstrated success as an individual producer, along with thorough knowledge of New York Life sales systems, products namely Life Insurance, Annuities, and New York Life's Financial Needs Analysis approach. • Must possess strong leadership qualities, excellent verbal and written communication skills with influencing others, and strong ability to problem solve, think critically and collaborate cross functionally. EOE M/F/D/V If you have difficulty using or interacting with any portions of this Web site due to incompatibility with an Assistive Technology, if you need the information in an alternative format, or if you have suggestions on how we can make this site more accessible, please contact us at: (212) 576-5811. * Based on revenue as reported by "Fortune 500, ranked within Industries, Insurance: Life, Health (Mutual)," Fortune Magazine, June 17, 2016. See http://fortune.com/fortune500/ for methodology. ** Total surplus, which includes the Asset Valuation Reserve, is one of the key indicators of the company's long-term financial strength and stability and is presented on a consolidated basis of the company. 1. Operating earnings is the key measure use by management to track Company's profitability from ongoing operations and underlying profitability of the business. This indicator is based on generally accepted accounting principles in the US (GAAP), with certain adjustments Company believes to be appropriate as a measurement approach (non GAAP), primarily the removal of gains or losses on investments and related adjustments. 2. Assets under management represent Consolidated Domestic and International insurance Company Statutory assets (cash and invested assets and separate account assets) and third party assets principally managed by New York Life Investment management Holdings LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of New York Life Insurance Company.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  New York Life Insurance</company>
      <jobid>02216273</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Sales &amp; Marketing| SENIOR ASSOCIATE, Sales and Retention Manager</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>SENIOR ASSOCIATE, Sales and Retention Manager</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  White Plains, NY, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  White Plains</city>
      <state>NY</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-CT-Greenwich-Associate_Technical_Writer.id01977067?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>d9d7027ae6bac11927f36b54e464c27f</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Associate Technical Writer</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Responsibilities Work as a part of the software development team to document new features and products Develop and maintain our trading software documentation and other technical communication to educate and support both internal stakeholders and developers, as well as our end clients Read and understand source code and test and validate use cases and existing tutorials/resources Distill project planning documentation and specifications from project leads and/or business analysts into a compact summary of new features and changes Identify gaps and new subject areas for documentation and gain support from stakeholders to create the content Qualifications 2+ year of experience writing and maintaining documentation for software systems Impeccable attention to detail At least basic knowledge of trading and financial products (especially derivatives) Ability to quickly grasp complex technical concepts and make them easily understandable in text and pictures Ability to read, understand, and communicate the function and behavior of code Experience writing clear and concise technical documentation for complex topics Fluency in communicating with different types of roles - you will be working closely with business analysts, project leads, and developers who will all have different communication styles - you will need to be comfortable with a variety of ways in which your colleagues communicate information Preferred Qualifications Computer science or engineering background Some experience or familiarity with Java and/or C++ Experience using or documenting trading software 4+ years of documenting software products for project leads and business analysts, including procedures, process documentation, and architecture descriptions Experience with Jira &amp; Confluence</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977067</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Information Technology| Associate Technical Writer</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Associate Technical Writer</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Greenwich, CT, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Greenwich</city>
      <state>CT</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-IL-Chicago-Customer_Service_Representative_-_Trade_Issues.id01977068?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>8a5e65d2ea944addf9ea430a24e848b9</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Customer Service Representative - Trade Issues</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Interactive Brokers is expanding its Trading Issues Department at our main retail call center in Chicago, IL. We are searching for experienced candidates with a prior background in the financial services industry, that are FINRA registered for the position of Customer Service Representative . The Trade Issues Customer Service Representative is accountable for providing a high level of client service to IB's existing retail and institutional clients. Our aim is thoroughly investigate trade inquiries, in particular, but also covers various other areas under the general customer service umbrella. [i] Figures as of March 31, 2017. Information on the company can be found at www.interactivebrokers.com Responsibilities Problem management with focus on wide scale service issues. Core competencies include, but are not limited to: trade and margin analysis, a wide range of products (cash market and derivatives) and global exchanges, order types, and transmission and execution inquiries. The candidate must possess general market knowledge in futures, options, and the equities markets. Previous customer service experience in a financial services or banking operations environment required. Investigate customer inquiries regarding trade-related issues (e.g., executions, position liquidations, order trigger conditions, trade cancellation requests, product availability &amp; attributes, order types and routing logic etc.) Assistance with trading platform operation and features; analyze and test existing systems and procedures in order to recommend and assist in the implementation enhancements Respond to inquiries, concerns and complaints from existing and prospective customers via telephone, e-mail, and on-line chat to achieve a solution that is mutually satisfactory while complying with policies, practices and procedures Must demonstrate excellent troubleshooting and problem resolution skills required to bring problems quickly to a resolution. Order status, settlement, exercise &amp; assignment, expiration processing, and corporate actions Qualifications Experience: 2 years financial industry experience with trading or brokerage services preferred; but will consider recent college graduate Education: Bachelor's degree in Finance, Economics, Business Administration or other related field Certification: Registrations: FINRA Series 7, 63 Computer: Strong PC technologies proficiency preferred; Microsoft Word &amp; Excel Strong quantitative analytical skills Excellent oral/written communication skills required</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977068</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Operations| Customer Service Representative - Trade Issues</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Customer Service Representative - Trade Issues</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Chicago, IL, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Chicago</city>
      <state>IL</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-NJ-Jersey_City-Corporate_Vice_President_Digital_Experience_-_Product_Owner.id02268840?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>3e65a4dac4f52b4d64f662d464906caa</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Corporate Vice President, Digital Experience - Product Owner</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>New York Life Insurance Company ("New York Life" or "the company") is the largest mutual life insurance company in the United States*. Founded in 1845, New York Life is headquartered in New York City, maintains offices in all fifty states, and owns Seguros Monterrey New York Life in Mexico. New York Life is one of the most financially strong and highly capitalized insurers in the business. The company reported 2016 operating earnings of $1.954 billion. Total assets under management at year end 2016, with affiliates, totaled $538 billion. As of year-end 2016, New York Life's surplus was $23.336 billion**. New York Life holds the highest possible financial strength ratings currently awarded to any life insurer from all four of the major ratings agencies: A.M. Best, A++; Fitch AAA; Moody's Aaa; Standard &amp; Poor's AA+. (Source: Individual Third Party Ratings Report as of 8/17/16). Financial strength, integrity and humanity-the values upon which New York Life was founded-have guided the company's decisions and actions for over 170 years. General Profile : This role will manage the development of CRM plans for Agency that integrate appropriate digital and outbound media including email, direct mail, social media, websites and traditional advertising. This role is responsible for conveying business requirements to the CRM development team, the vision of the new CRM roll out, the training of a new platform and communication of this vision to Agency and the field. This role will work closely with developers, testers, managers and senior management. In addition, this role will manage the launch, strategic direction and tactics for CRM programs. Functional Knowledge: • Bachelors Degree • Minimum of 5-7 years relevant experience. • Strong in depth knowledge of Agency and the state of the business today including visions and challenges. • Avid user of technology and a deep interest in technology solutions. • Strategically strong and able to connect business challenges and CRM strategy/tactics. • Understanding of Agile Methodology. • Ability to build relationships within Agency and Field leadership. • Understands business processes of field managers and agents. • Business Savvy. Problem Solving : Ability to communicate business requirements to application development teams and make decisions on behalf of user population. Understand the challenges and solve problems accordingly. Decision Making/ Nature of Impact : Empowered to make decisions, solicit input from others but needs to make the decisions quickly. Communication Requirements : Ability to communicate business requirements to technology teams. Requires working closely with key stakeholders throughout the organization and beyond to communicate different messages at any given time. EOE M/F/D/V If you have difficulty using or interacting with any portions of this Web site due to incompatibility with an Assistive Technology, if you need the information in an alternative format, or if you have suggestions on how we can make this site more accessible, please contact us at: (212) 576-5811. * Based on revenue as reported by "Fortune 500, ranked within Industries, Insurance: Life, Health (Mutual)," Fortune Magazine, June 17, 2016. See http://fortune.com/fortune500/ for methodology. ** Total surplus, which includes the Asset Valuation Reserve, is one of the key indicators of the company's long-term financial strength and stability and is presented on a consolidated basis of the company. 1. Operating earnings is the key measure use by management to track Company's profitability from ongoing operations and underlying profitability of the business. This indicator is based on generally accepted accounting principles in the US (GAAP), with certain adjustments Company believes to be appropriate as a measurement approach (non GAAP), primarily the removal of gains or losses on investments and related adjustments. 2. Assets under management represent Consolidated Domestic and International insurance Company Statutory assets (cash and invested assets and separate account assets) and third party assets principally managed by New York Life Investment management Holdings LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of New York Life Insurance Company.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  New York Life Insurance</company>
      <jobid>02268840</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Insurance| Corporate Vice President, Digital Experience - Product Owner</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Corporate Vice President, Digital Experience - Product Owner</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Jersey City, NJ, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Jersey City</city>
      <state>NJ</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-IL-Chicago-Junior_Compliance_Associate_-_SecuritiesCommodities.id01977044?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>e0a97addc3320c74968687b41c69e882</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Junior Compliance Associate - Securities/Commodities</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>Overview Interactive Brokers is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing brokers. Our clients have access to more than 100 market centers in 25 countries from a single account. We are the lowest cost provider of brokerage services and the largest U.S. electronic broker based on daily average revenue trades executing 657,000 trades per day (First Quarter 2017 results). At Interactive Brokers, you will be part of a dynamic, multinational, fast paced, results oriented team working to provide our customers with state-of-the-art trading technology, superior execution capabilities, worldwide electronic access, and sophisticated risk management tools. Interactive Brokers , a Global Securities and Commodities business leader and one of the largest financial services firms in the U.S. has an immediate need for a Compliance Associate in our Chicago office. This position has excellent growth potential for highly motivated and exceptional performers. The ideal candidate some regulatory compliance experience working for an exchange, a regulatory organization, a Broker Dealer (BD), a Futures Commission Merchant (FCM) or similar organization. Other acceptable experience would include internal audit, legal, accounting or other control function of a financial services firm or regulator. In the absence of direct industry experience, we will also consider applicants with excellent Bachelor's-level educational credentials who have some background in accounting, computer science or similar areas with strong analytical and quantitative skills. Responsibilities Investigating factual and regulatory rule background behind client trading and financial activity Preparing and drafting regulatory correspondence Creating, reviewing and following up on surveillance reports of financial and trading activity Preparing regulatory filings Assisting with Anti-Money Laundering Program Developing knowledge about the firm's computer systems and trading processes Qualifications Must have a college degree with strong grades; acceptable majors include: Finance, Accounting, Computer Science or Information Systems Must be a detail-oriented person Have the ability to understand regulatory rules and client financial activity and trading strategies. High proficiency with desktop applications and MS Office suite of products is required. Knowledge of UNIX, SQL, Perl is a plus. Must be comfortable working in an automated, hands-on environment. Excellent written and oral communication skill sets are important prerequisites.</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  Interactive Brokers</company>
      <jobid>01977044</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Compliance/Legal| Junior Compliance Associate - Securities/Commodities</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Junior Compliance Associate - Securities/Commodities</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  Chicago, IL, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  Chicago</city>
      <state>IL</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.efinancialcareers.com/jobs-USA-NY-New_York-Corporate_Vice_President_Director_Strategy__Internal_Consulting.id02216269?query=cGFnZT0xJnBhZ2VTaXplPTI0JnNlYXJjaE1vZGU9REVGQVVMVF9TRUFSQ0gmam9iU2VhcmNoSWQ9UWpoR09EZ3dOamt4T0RNeU9ERkZOemN4T0VNM05qZzNNVEkwUkVKRFFqUXVNVFV3TnpjM01UY3dOekUxTXk0dE1UUTFNamM0T0RVM05RJTNEJTNEJmZpbHRlckdyb3VwRm9ybS5pbmNsdWRlUmVmcmVzaGVkPXRydWU%3D</pageurl>
<record>
      <uniq_id>9db90e3f9f6829508e6904b9e4e48266</uniq_id>
      <jobtitle>Corporate Vice President (Director), Strategy &amp; Internal Consulting</jobtitle>
      <jobdescription>New York Life Insurance Company ("New York Life" or "the company") is the largest mutual life insurance company in the United States*. Founded in 1845, New York Life is headquartered in New York City and maintains offices in all fifty states. New York Life is one of the most financially strong and highly capitalized insurers in the business. The company holds the highest possible financial strength ratings currently awarded to any life insurer**. Financial strength, integrity and humanity-the values upon which New York Life was founded-have guided the company's decisions and actions for over 170 years. Our primary business areas are Life Insurance, Retirement and Investments supported by an industry leading Career Agency Distribution channel, Direct to Consumer channel and Third Party Distribution channels. New York Life is seeking a highly qualified individual to join the Strategy &amp; Internal Consulting team based in New York, NY. Position Overview The Strategy &amp; Internal Consulting (S&amp;IC) team, reporting into the President of New York Life, works closely with the CEO and the Executive Leadership Team to help define &amp; articulate business strategy and support oversight and execution of key enterprise strategic initiatives and other large / complex programs. This team works closely with Finance and other key stakeholders to drive the annual planning process. The team also supports key decision-making forums and senior executive meetings e.g., Executive Management Committee, Board of Directors, etc. The S&amp;IC team often partners with Senior Leaders in the various business and functional areas to support development and execution of strategic initiatives within those areas. The team's role typically includes framing and analyzing complex business problems, developing recommendations, partnering with line managers to drive implementation, facilitating governance and communication processes, and playing a key role in informing and influencing decision making. The Strategy &amp; Internal Consulting team comprises high performing individuals with strong academic credentials and professional experiences with backgrounds in management consulting &amp; industry. Role Description Thought Leadership &amp; Advisory • Frame and analyze complex problems • Assess areas of opportunity, in line with overall vision and strategy • Develop pragmatic solutions to key strategic and operational issues • Develop &amp; present recommendations to senior leadership • Play a key role in informing and influencing senior management decision making Strategic Planning Office &amp; Executive Communication • Support strategic planning processes, including interdependencies between key business, technology and financial planning processes • Facilitate structured reviews of the enterprise portfolio of strategic initiatives &amp; implications (e.g., budget considerations, resource allocation, etc.) • Support agenda and materials development for senior executive audiences &amp; meetings e.g., Board Meetings, Executive Offsites, etc. Project Leadership • Approach projects holistically, owning and driving end-to-end delivery of solutions • Lead implementation of key enterprise initiatives by forming collaborative partnerships with colleagues across businesses and functional areas • Manage enterprise governance and communication processes Desired Qualifications We are looking for outstanding individuals with excellent intellectual &amp; analytical capabilities, pragmatic problem solving skills, strong communications &amp; influencing capabilities, a robust strategy &amp; change management toolkit and a passion to effect change across the organization at the most senior levels. - Bachelor's degree required, MBA or advanced degree strongly preferred - 7-8+ years overall experience, 3-5 years in top-tier management consulting firm - Outstanding critical thinking, analytical and quantitative abilities - Strong communication skills including experience in developing C-suite presentations - Experience in financial services preferred, insurance expertise is a plus - Experience in structuring &amp; delivering technology strategy projects and a broad understanding of current technology practices (Agile, Cloud Computing/SaaS, Enterprise Data Management, etc.) &amp; emerging trends (Robotics/AI, InsurTech, etc.) is desired - Collaborative work style / leadership presence with ability to effectively interact with &amp; earn trust of peers and senior management across the organization - Project and process management skills, including proven ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously - Executive presence; self-starter with a keen sense of ownership and commitment to the work, and a passion to deliver results Location: New York, NY Supervisor: Vice President (Managing Director), Head of Strategy &amp; Internal Consulting * Fortune 500 Ranked within Industries, Insurance: Life and Health (Mutual), June 2016. ** Independent rating Agencies, as of 6/9/16: A.M. Best (A++), Fitch (AAA), Moody's Investors Service (Aaa), Standard &amp; Poor's (AA+). The financial strength and ratings do not apply to any investment products which are subject to market risks and will fluctuate in value. SF: LI-KV1 EOE M/F/D/V</jobdescription>
      <postdate>11 Oct 17</postdate>
      <site_name>www.efinancialcareers.com</site_name>
      <company>  New York Life Insurance</company>
      <jobid>02216269</jobid>
      <employmenttype_jobstatus>Job Type:  Permanent, Full time</employmenttype_jobstatus>
      <jobcategory>jobs| Insurance| Corporate Vice President (Director), Strategy &amp; Internal Consulting</jobcategory>
      <jobsubcategory>Corporate Vice President (Director), Strategy &amp; Internal Consulting</jobsubcategory>
      <joblocation_address>  New York, NY, USA</joblocation_address>
      <city>  New York</city>
      <state>NY</state>
      <ratetime_interval>Yearly</ratetime_interval>
    </record>
</page>
</root>
