<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474454400</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>2085669ba2bc8f28de692273f546c6b8</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474454400</page_url>
      <job_title>Registered Nurse (Gastroenterology)</job_title>
      <job_description> Chalmers P. Wylie VA Ambulatory Care Center is seeking a Gastroenterology (GI) RN for the Surgery Services. Duty location is at the Columbus Ambulatory Care Center. This RN will provide safe, prompt, and skillful nursing care for patients with gastrointestinal needs. Minimum qualifications include 2-3 years of successful nursing practice. The incumbent must have excellent customer service skills and work well in teams. Basic Life Support (BLS) and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS) Certification is required.
Work Schedule: Monday through Friday 8:00 am to 4:30 pmFunctional Statement Title/#: Functional Statement/Registered Nurse (Gastroenterology)</job_description>
      <location>Columbus, OH</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(614)257-5867</phone_number>
      <salary>$50,700 to $99,985</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-18</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474340300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>0279273902c719a3a04a63359dadf785</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474340300</page_url>
      <job_title>Supervisory Procurement Analyst</job_title>
      <job_description>Provide authoritative analytical support and advice to the Procurement Services Executive DISA in the areas of contracting policies and procurement planning.
	Conducts procurement compliance reviews including internal and external Procurement Management Reviews (PMRs)
	Oversee the execution of contract administration functions, including quality assurance and policy administration. 
	Develops  information so that management judgments can be made on the adequacy of the of the acquisition programs.</job_description>
      <location>Maryland City, MD</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Defense</sector>
      <organization>Department of Defense</organization>
      <phone_number>(317) 212-4737</phone_number>
      <salary>$131,767 to $161,900</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474524900</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>719d81df97f10ab147bb6f4b48f132bb</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474524900</page_url>
      <job_title>Lead HR Specialist</job_title>
      <job_description>Lead Human Resources Specialist (Recruitment/Placement), GS-0201-12 - The incumbent executes full performance HR Specialty level work, same type of work in Recruitment and Placement performed by the team. Incumbent functions as team leader for the Title 5/Title 38/Hybrid Title 38 Customer Service, and Operation Divisions. The incumbent serves a team lead, advises and performs first line review of work completed by lower graded junior specialists and assistants assigned to their team. Participates in special initiatives, studies and projects, and Career Development activities. Participates in initiatives, studies and projects such as self-assessment reviews, pre-Reduction-In-Force exercises, the student and summer employment recruitment programs, application of draft qualification standards, etc. Works with other Human Resources specialists in identifying potential program initiatives or special projects that could improve the use of civilian human resources, solve problems, or enhance program effectiveness, provides written reports and briefings outlining findings and recommendations, and coordinates results with activities both within and outside the HR Office.

MAJOR DUTIES:

	Ensure that the organizations strategic plan, mission, vision and values are communicated to the team and integrated into the teams strategies, goals, objectives, work plans and work products and services.
	Articulate and communicate to the team the assignment, project, problems to be solved, actionable events, milestones, and/or program issues under review, and deadlines and time frames for completion.
	Coach the team in the selection and application of appropriate problem solving methods and techniques, provide advice on work methods, practices and procedures, and assist the team and/or individual members in identifying the parameters of a viable solution.
	Lead the team in: identifying, distributing and balancing workload and tasks among employees in accordance with established work flow, skill level and/or occupational specialization.
	Making adjustments to accomplish the workload in accordance with established priorities to ensure timely accomplishment of assigned team tasks.
	Ensuring that each employee has an integral role in developing the final team product.
	Train or arrange for the training of team members in methods and techniques of team building and working in teams to accomplish tasks or projects, and provide or arrange for specific administrative or technical training necessary for accomplishment of individual and team tasks.
	Monitor and report on the status and progress of work, checking on work in progress and reviewing completed work to see that the supervisors instructions on work priorities, methods, deadlines and quality have been met.
	Serve as coach, facilitator and/or negotiator in coordinating team initiatives and in consensus building activities among team members.
	Represent the team in dealings with the supervisor or manager for the purpose of obtaining resources (e.g., computer hardware and software, use of overtime or compensatory time), and securing needed information or decisions from the supervisor on major work problems and issues that arise.
	Report to the supervisor periodically on team and individual work accomplishments, problems, progress in mastering tasks.
	Estimate and report to the team on progress in meeting established milestones and deadlines for completion of assignments, projects and tasks, and ensure that all team members are aware of and participate in planning for achievement of team goals and objectives.
	Lead the team in assessing its strengths and weaknesses and provide leadership to the team in exploring alternatives and determining what improvements can be made (e.g., in work methods, processes and procedures).
	Resolve simple, informal complaints of employees and refer others, such as formal grievances and appeals, to the supervisor or an appropriate management official.
	Maintain program and administrative reference materials, project files and relevant background documents and make available policies, procedures and written instructions from the supervisor; maintain current knowledge to answer questions from team members on procedures, policies, directives, etc.
	Intercede with the supervisor on behalf of the team to inform the supervisor of performance management issues/problems and to recommend/request related actions, such as: assignments, reassignments, promotions, tour of duty changes, peer reviews and performance appraisals.
	All other duties as assigned.

Work schedule: Monday - Friday, 8:00 a.m. to 4:30 p.m.
Compressed/Flexible Schedule: NOT AVAILABLE
Telework: NOT AVAILABLE
Virtual: This NOT a virtual position.
Position Description Title/PD#: Lead HR Specialist/ PD# 573-05625-A. The PD is available for viewing in HR Office in trailer T11 Mon. - Fri. 7:30 a.m. &amp; 5:00 p.m
A Relocation Incentive of $5000 is offered for a two (2) year commitment agreement.</job_description>
      <location>Gainesville, FL</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(352) 548-6009</phone_number>
      <salary>$72,168 to $93,821</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-24</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474531300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>cde79215147873c9ee740e7f3e257bc4</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474531300</page_url>
      <job_title>Auditor</job_title>
      <job_description>Serves as an Auditor with primary responsibility for developing, planning, defining objectives, and coordinating audits, assignments or special projects of world-wide Army Morale, Welfare, and Recreation systems and programs. Applies professional techniques and methodology in making audits of diversified programs and activities that use different funds, accounting, and control systems. Uses in-depth professional knowledge, judgment and ingenuity in problem solving or analysis of programs which are broad in scope, complex, and interrelated, in an area of accounting or auditing where the internal review evaluator functions as a designated authority. Performs the most complex analysis and evaluations related to all aspects of accounting, management control and risk management. Provides assistance, advice and technical guidance in correcting deficiencies, solving complex management control or financial problems, and interpreting laws, regulations and procedures. Develops and applies advance techniques for evaluating problem areas. Suggests revisions of operational procedures in order to conform with audit recommendations and evaluates actions reported to have been taken with respect to deficient conditions reflected in audit reports which will improve program management within IMCOM G9and the Army. Resolves conflicts which may arise. Considered a technical expert in the professional field of auditing. Utilizes professional accounting and audit skills to maintain oversight for implementing appropriate laws, directives, and regulations of internal control programs and procedures. These programs are to ensure there are no vulnerable areas. Documents the results in accordance with Comptroller General Standards, DoD and DA policies. Applies Comptroller General Standards and a wide range of evaluation techniques (e.g., interviews, computer assisted techniques, statistical analysis and questionnaires) in gathering, documenting, and summarizing data. Provides advice to top managers that directly affect the overall mission of IMCOM G9. Makes audit reports or special reports on completed assignments which are sent to the Commanding General or through him to higher echelons within the Department of Army and Department of Defense. Reports are considered professionally authoritative. Communicates directly with HQDA, DOD, other government agencies, and external audit agencies concerning all aspects of actions. Completed work reviewed for fulfillment of objectives, effectiveness, and the effect of recommendations on other IMCOM G9 program objectives.</job_description>
      <location>San Antonio, TX</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(210) 466-1478</phone_number>
      <salary>$85,000 to $100,000</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474419700</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>ec9da721e69d7df08fd6fd952edf3152</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474419700</page_url>
      <job_title>SUPERVISORY AUDITOR</job_title>
      <job_description>As a SUPERVISORY AUDITOR, GS-0511-13, you will:

	Incumbent has responsibility for the work of assigned personnel. Performs the full range of supervisory and managerial responsibilities. Assigns work to functional staff members in accordance with established organization mission and functions, workload fluctuations and personnel availability.
	Supervises complex analysis and evaluations related to all aspects of accounting, performance management, management control, and risk management.  Applies a comprehensive knowledge of analysis/reporting requirements, work processes, accounting systems structure and data produced to resolve significant  accounting and management problems.
	Interprets financial policies and procedures generated by higher headquarters to include implications of immediate and long-range management activities, plans  and decisions.
	Supervises a variety of reviews that are usually without precedent and require the use of advanced auditing, analytical, and financial review techniques in  gathering and evaluating pertinent data.
	Serves as the command representative and point of contact for external agencies (GAO,USAAA, DODIG, CPAs, etc.) regarding their evaluations, surveys, and/or audit findings and recommendations.
	Performs other duties as assigned.

Do to the limitations placed on this website, all listed duties under this position could not be provided. If you would like the complete list of duties, please contact the POC of this announcement.</job_description>
      <location>Indianapolis, IN</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(317) 247-3300</phone_number>
      <salary>$86,406 to $112,326</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-28</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474160300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>449919705b607aab03cc1033d763aef3</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474160300</page_url>
      <job_title>INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPEC (INFOSEC/SYSADMIN)</job_title>
      <job_description>The successful selectee will perform the following duties:

	Implementing standard operating procedures &amp; configuration control for GOTS/COTS &amp; customized software to ensure appropriate levels of compliance/security.
	Developing and acquiring systems software tools/support services to assignment/management of passwords, user IDs &amp; other software security mechanisms to ensure TPI.
	Administrating some or all of the following disciplines: Windows XP/07, Windows Server 03/08, Linux, UNIX, ARINC, Cisco Voice and Video, Cisco ASA, Cisco Routers and Switches, CISCO Works, Whats Up Gold, Cisco NIDS, TACAS, SPLUNK, Oracle database support (status checks, monitoring, critical patch updates, and Advanced Security), Oracle Recovery Manager (RMAN) experience for backup and recovery to include hot and cold backups.
	Implementing systems security plans and policies and preventive maintenance schedules.
	Troubleshooting security threats and vulnerabilities in response to incident reports.
	Selecting, installing, and monitoring the performance of appropriate security tools, including firewalls, intrusion detection systems, and vulnerability self-assessment programs.
	Conducting risk and vulnerability assessments of planned and installed information systems to identify vulnerabilities, risks, and protection needs.</job_description>
      <location>Bangor, WA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>800-378-4559</phone_number>
      <salary>$77,926 to $120,461</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474416800</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>13586da224187fb2f3653dc2f21bb642</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474416800</page_url>
      <job_title>Human Resources Specialist (Recruitment and Placement)</job_title>
      <job_description>Provides advisory services on recruitment and placement
actions requiring identification and analysis of management staffing problems,
and development of solutions considering the total personnel management
viewpoint.  Exercises persuasiveness,
imagination and insight in preparing and presenting recommendations to
management.  Advises management of recruitment
strategies, sources and special programs which emphasize affirmative action and
outreach in staffing positions.  Makes
suggestions and offer advice concerning the best-qualified candidates in
keeping with VA staffing goals and programs. 
Assist in developing short and long range staffing plans to forecast
mission requirements, assess employee turnover patterns, review past
recruitment practices, technological changes and local market conditions.
Participates as an advisor and consultant to management officials, influences
and persuades the acceptance and exercise of sound personnel management
concepts, practices and personnel innovations. 
Consults and participates with all members of management in analyzing
the broad implications of higher levels of authority, laws, regulations,
policies, as well as technological and administrative advancement trends
associated with a viable Human Resources Program.

Work Schedule:8:00 am to 4:30 pmPosition Description Title/PD#: Human Resource Specialist, 6261A</job_description>
      <location>Denver, CO</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Only</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(303)202-7959</phone_number>
      <salary>$78,183 to $101,641</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-28</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474464300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>4291bce762f5e50054d5d9502c476029</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474464300</page_url>
      <job_title>Civil Engineer</job_title>
      <job_description>The Federal Energy Regulatory Commission is seeking a highly motivated and qualified candidate for an exciting full-time permanent position within the Division of Dam Safety and Inspections of the Office of Energy Projects. The position is located in the San Francisco Regional Office. The incumbent will work as a civil engineer and must be knowledgeable in the investigation, design, construction, operation, and maintenance of dams and hydroelectric power facilities, applying one or more of the following disciplines of civil engineering to the investigation, design, construction, operation, and maintenance of dams and hydroelectric power facilities: structural, hydrologic, geotechnical and/or engineering geology. Assignments may require substantial travel and can involve hiking in mountainous terrain, climbing steeply inclined faces of dams, and descending into dam galleries, penstocks, and tunnels. The ability to communicate effectively with others is also important. The Federal Energy Regulatory Commission assists consumers in obtaining reliable, efficient and sustainable energy services at a reasonable cost through appropriate regulatory and market means. To learn more about the Commission, please visit www.ferc.gov.The duties of the position are:- Inspection, engineering evaluation and analyses of hydroelectric projects including dams to ensure the safety of the projects.- Inspection, engineering evaluation and analyses of hydroelectric projects to ensure compliance with the terms of the license, the provisions of the Federal Power Act, and the Commission's regulations.- Prepares engineering reports to establish and document the dam safety, public safety and environmental and license compliance of the hydroelectric project.Duties and responsibilities at the GS-12 level may be of less complexity.</job_description>
      <location>San Francisco, CA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Energy</sector>
      <organization>Department of Energy</organization>
      <phone_number>202-502-6152</phone_number>
      <salary>$86,663 to $133,967</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-28</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474496000</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>bd29d7c4d9798ba40beb8010991ee91f</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474496000</page_url>
      <job_title>HUMAN RESOURCES SPECIALIST (MILITARY/INFORMATION SYSTEMS)</job_title>
      <job_description> ·        The primary purpose of this position is to serve as Personnel Systems Manager (PSM) and to direct the management of the Personnel Data System (PDS). This is an Air Reserve Technician (ART) position.·        Plans, directs, controls all aspects of the Personnel Data Systems (PDS). Manages, directs, and controls the operation of the PDS to include the Military Personnel Data System (MiLPDS), Virtual Personnel Center (vPC), Personnel Records Display Application (PRDA) Enterprise Output Manager(EOM) and others; and related systems interfaces.·        Plans and provides customers assistance/training. Promotes the use of PDS by providing instruction to functional area users on automated applications and systems.·        Provides military personnel advisory services to commanders and staff on all personnel systems programs; provides staff advisory guidance and technical assistance to commanders and management officials requiring or requesting access or utilization of information contained in the various PDS.The position may be filled at the GS-09TO11 OR GS-11 .The individual selected for this position may be promoted to the target level without further competition upon meeting any legal and regulatory requirements.</job_description>
      <location>Whiteman AFB, MO</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Air Force</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Air Force</organization>
      <phone_number>(800)525-0102</phone_number>
      <salary>$49,994 to $78,630</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-21</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474556100</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>62a1b3c49fb78aad44b0282d39c71ff0</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474556100</page_url>
      <job_title>Contract Specialist, GS-1102-12</job_title>
      <job_description>-Prepare contracting officer decisions relating to protests and disputes.-Establish acquisition plans, milestones, and acquisition strategies including developing  solicitation cost accounting standards, warranties, liquidated damages, advance payments, rights in data, safety requirements, and other provisions.-Perform cost/price analysis, including cost breakdowns to determine reasonableness, allocability, and allowability. -Administer contracts until final delivery and payment are completed and the contract is changed out, in addition to negotiating and executing contract modifications (if contracting officer) or preparing modifications for execution by the contracting officer.</job_description>
      <location>Lakewood, CO</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Interior</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Interior</organization>
      <phone_number>303-445-2684</phone_number>
      <salary>$78,183 to $101,641</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-28</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474414600</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>f257aa853cd71c184cc5df7b959d4161</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474414600</page_url>
      <job_title>Registered Nurse- Patient Aligned Care Team (PACT)</job_title>
      <job_description>THIS POSITION IS LOCATED IN GREENVILLE, NCThe Registered Nurses for
the Patient Aligned Care Team (PACT) Clinic will function as a primary care nurse in support of the
physician or mid-level provider.  Duties
will include, but not be limited to, oversight of nursing staff, patient
intake, documentation, point of care testing and health screening.  The RN will assess, triage, take histories
and document conditions and concerns for veterans presenting to the clinic in
person and via the telephone.  The
clinical nurse will coordinate care through the health continuum.  Patient/health education, health coaching and
health promotion are integral functions of the role.Tour of Duty:  Full-Time; Monday through Friday 8:00am-4:30pm. In order to meet mission needs, you may be required to work alternate work schedules. These alternate work schedules include, but are not limited to, evenings, weekends and holidays.</job_description>
      <location>Greenville, NC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(919)286-6858</phone_number>
      <salary>$54,303 to $104,918</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474362200</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>5b0a097d33451ad66a4a116496d70d09</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474362200</page_url>
      <job_title>Civil Engineer</job_title>
      <job_description>You will prepare civil preliminary and final designs, analysis, and layouts for developing various civil features of work for navigation, flood control, local flood protection projects and other projects, and evaluate, advise, and resolve problems, issues, and conditions with these projects.
	You will coordinate civil engineering and design projects which involve site layouts, laydown areas, grading, roadways and other site features based on unique site conditions.
	You will inspect ongoing and completed work; document all observations and developing correspondence to convey the condition of the project or work.
	You will represent the District on matters related to the lock and dam navigation structures, channels, associated facilities, and activities on the Allegheny/Monongahela/Ohio River navigation system as well as flood control structures by actively participating in conferences, hearings, or presentations involving program issues.
	You will conduct comprehensive studies and develop general designs of portions of civil works engineering projects. The studies will include researching, compiling, and analyzing data such as design requirements, topographic maps, field surveys of project areas, past inspections reports, and land use practices.
	You will perform the necessary management and coordination tasks to include preparation of internal and external correspondence, schedules, determining funding requirements, monitoring expenditures, coordinating various work features within and outside the section to include outside private and public interests.
	You will prepare preliminary and final designs, analyses, layouts and computations for features of the aforementioned projects for preparation of contract drawings, specifications, quantities, and engineering documents such as design memorandums.
	You will provide support to the construction and operations functions to include review of contractor submitted drawings for conformance with the design, contract plans and specifications, making visits to projects under construction to determine if field conditions and construction are consistent with the intent of the design, attending meetings and conferences with Corps personnel and contractors relative to construction projects.
	You will prepare technical sections of contracts for Architecture/Engineer services including detailed estimates of proposed A/E fees for use in negotiations. Participates in the negotiations of A/E contracts.
	You will conduct site investigations of existing facilities to identify erosion, structural defects, sedimentation, or other issues with maintaining continued operations of the facility.</job_description>
      <location>Pittsburgh, PA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$61,675 to $96,104</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474161800</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>8ad86006ff55188a05941bbce4947a6a</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474161800</page_url>
      <job_title>COMPUTER SCIENTIST</job_title>
      <job_description>Duties will vary based on Position Description and Grade Level.  This series includes professional positions which primarily involve the application of, or research into, computer science methods and techniques to store, manipulate, transform or present information by means of computer systems.  The primary requirements of the work are (a) professional competence in applying the theoretical foundations of computer science, including computer system architecture and system software organization, the representation and transformation of information structures, and the theoretical models for such representations and transformations; (b) specialized knowledge of the design characteristics, limitations, and potential applications of systems having the ability to transform information, and of broad areas of applications of computing which have common structures, processes, and techniques; and (c) knowledge of relevant mathematical and statistical sciences.Typical functions performed by Computer Scientists include:--development of software systems using a knowledge of techniques, procedures, and processes such as operating system theory, data structure, computer system architecture, Software engineering, and computer communications--development of computer graphic systems using a knowledge of graphic display systems, general purpose graphics languages, and optimization techniques involving preprocessors graphical algorithms, memory management methods, and high-speed communication links--development of high-speed computing systems and real time data acquisition systems--development of integrated computer systems using a knowledge of computer software and hardware concepts, and mathematics--development of problem-oriented and nonprocedural languages and their translating/operating systems, construction of input-output buffering schemes, and design of automatic scheduling and monitoring methods to increase scope and effectiveness of computer applications--development of advanced concepts of automation and information processing display, control and transfer</job_description>
      <location>Corona, CA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>(800)378-4559</phone_number>
      <salary>$32,844 to $63,517</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-09-30</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474354300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>99c188d421c6fd944646d0c8c5433543</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474354300</page_url>
      <job_title>Nurse(Clinical/Case Management)</job_title>
      <job_description>As a Nurse (Clinical/Case Management), you will:Provide advanced practice clinical nursing, administrative and organizational skills in managing the continuity of care for the beneficiary populations.Educate both the patient and members of the healthcare delivery team about case management, healthcare and treatment options, community resources, insurance benefits, psychosocial concerns, etc., so that informed decisions can be made.Engage in problem solving by exploring options to care when available and alternative plans when necessary to achieve desired outcomes.Provide oversight and input to nursing practice matters.Provide guidance on establishing appointment protocols to match patients' needs with available resources in a timely manner.</job_description>
      <location>Fort Sam Houston, TX</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$79,905 to $100,251</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-19</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/473852100</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>8f0dd3c8b7caa4f32eab485d64a6520a</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/473852100</page_url>
      <job_title>CONTRACT PRICE/COST ANALYST</job_title>
      <job_description> 

Major
duties for this position include, but are not limited to:

·        
Resolving
critical problems that develop after contract placement, such as arriving at
equitable adjustments in the contract price or delivery schedules; addressing
major increases in the total estimated cost limitation, or addressing vendor
performance issues.·        
Preparing
an audit summary for submission to the contractor if proprietary issues prevent
the contractor from conducting its own subcontract audits.·        
Reviewing
and/or preparing contract documentation (i.e. technical, production, or audit
reports, or Provision Item Orders).·        
Reviewing
and assessing the quality of the prime contractor's evaluation of direct and
indirect subcontractor costs.  Advising
the contractor on the quality and effectiveness of its cost/price and technical
analysis of its subcontract proposals, and advising the Contracting Office
and/or negotiator to assist in development of Government negotiation
objectives.·        
Evaluating contractor proposals and making determinations of
adequacy as well as ensuring that the contractor is notified timely of any inadequate
proposals and the documentation required for further proposal evaluation.·        
Coordinating,
informing, and briefing significant proposal issues and delays with the Chief of the
Contracting Office, Business Operations Department, SSGR as well as program
offices and projects representatives.</job_description>
      <location>Groton, CT</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>years</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>(800)378-4559</phone_number>
      <salary>$95,147 to $123,689</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474366400</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>a8f6cc0c7fdeae4bad845949285fb678</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474366400</page_url>
      <job_title>Supervisory Contract Specialist, NH-1102-04</job_title>
      <job_description>Plans organizes and oversees the activities of the organization, developing goals and objectives that integrate organization and functional area objectives.Serves as the senior civilian business advisor in the organization with unlimited warrant authority.Serves as the Competition Advocate, Business/Contract Clearance Authority and/or Small Business Representative for the organization or installation consistent with FAR, as supplemented.Represents the organization with a variety of installation and functional area organizations.</job_description>
      <location>Hanscom AFB, MA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Air Force</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Air Force</organization>
      <phone_number>(937)257-6983</phone_number>
      <salary>$111,695 to $161,900</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-21</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474470500</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>4332bc2eb79c7aa959533a3c64a1673b</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474470500</page_url>
      <job_title>Physical Scientist (Quality Assurance Specialist), GS-1301-12/13 (DEU-TERM-CNS)</job_title>
      <job_description>As a Physical Scientist (Quality Assurance Specialist) within the Eastern Energy Resource Science Center, some of your specific duties will include: Evaluates research laboratories for proper quality assurance (QA)/quality control (QC) practices and/or procedures, and for compliance with a Quality Management System (QMS).Assists laboratories with implementing modifications to laboratory practices and/or procedures to ensure compliance with QMS.Provides professional QA knowledge in research laboratories.Provides training, QA support, and performs root cause analyses, pre-audits, and corrective actions to implement a QA program.Assists with documenting and monitoring proper use of analytical equipment.Collaborates effectively as part of a multidisciplinary team of geologists, geochemists, physical scientists, and/or engineers.Demonstrates excellent communication skills and ability to present quality assurance findings and results in a clear and concise manner.Works with specialist(s) to conduct research and laboratory proficiency testing, create documentation of capabilities, and resolve internal and external audit deficiencies.</job_description>
      <location>Reston, VA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Full-Time</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Interior</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Interior</organization>
      <phone_number>303-236-9577</phone_number>
      <salary>$79,720 to $123,234</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474362300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>2ef48f5956531d4534eb81c22b5660e4</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474362300</page_url>
      <job_title>Nurse (Advanced Practice Registered Nurse Practitioner/Family Practice)</job_title>
      <job_description>As a Family Nurse Practitioner, you will:Provide independent and collaborative specialty, comprehensive and therapeutic health care services, integrating the art and science of nursing into medical practice.Performed acute, non-acute and chronic clinical and psychological diagnosis.Formulate a therapeutic plan of care in collaboration with specialty physicians.Provide counseling to patients and their families for prevention of illness and maintenance of health, in order to assist patients in attaining physical, mental, and social well-being.</job_description>
      <location>Fort Bragg, NC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$109,265 to $135,599</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-24</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474420900</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>67c3479cd7dfd6c959f1dce8f9ec8c62</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474420900</page_url>
      <job_title>Natural/Cultural Resource Programs Manager (Interdisciplinary Position)</job_title>
      <job_description>As the Natural/Cultural Resource Programs Manager (Interdisciplinary Position) in this position, you will: Serve as a Natural and Cultural Resource Programs Manager.Provide extensive environmental expertise to support assigned environmental projects through application of professional knowledge and skill in all the Wildlife and Cultural Resources practices, processes and techniques.Execute assigned projects, in-house and by contract, to comply with all applicable Federal, State, and Local Environmental laws and policies.Coordinate curricula and training for assigned program areas at the installation.Provide advisory services on questions, issues, and projects in assigned program areas.Comply with health, safety, and environmental rules and procedures, and perform work that enhances the safety of the work environment.Click here to preview the
questionnaire for this position: View Assessment Questions.</job_description>
      <location>Shaw AFB, SC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Air Force</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Air Force</organization>
      <phone_number>(202)422-7256</phone_number>
      <salary>$60,210 to $78,270</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-21</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474515700</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>df5d79c946f1d8939c98c6da556f136b</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474515700</page_url>
      <job_title>Regional Economist ZP 0110-3/4 (MAP)</job_title>
      <job_description>At the ZP-4, the individual selected for this position will....Provide technical leadership to teams responsible for the production of nationally consistent data on the U.S. Ocean and Great Lakes economy using established methods.Provide expertise to managers and partners regarding economic data, analysis methodologies, projects, and strategic partnerships.Research and formulate plans to aid in the application of economic data and methodology to coastal resource management issues.  Provide input on ecosystem services research on non-market valuation methods and data.Communicate economic data, concepts, and research results to non-technical audiences.Develop strategies for both short and long-range planning in consultation with higher-level officialsThe ZP-3 is developmental leading to the performance of the above duties.</job_description>
      <location>Charleston Naval Center, SC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Commerce</sector>
      <organization>Department of Commerce</organization>
      <phone_number>(571) 414-3492</phone_number>
      <salary>$60,210 to $131,833</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-08-04</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474288300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>714e359bef8144ba4d29174b8cd22788</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474288300</page_url>
      <job_title>COMPUTER SCIENTIST</job_title>
      <job_description>Duties will vary based on Position Description and Grade Level.  This series includes professional positions which primarily involve the application of, or research into, computer science methods and techniques to store, manipulate, transform or present information by means of computer systems.  The primary requirements of the work are (a) professional competence in applying the theoretical foundations of computer science, including computer system architecture and system software organization, the representation and transformation of information structures, and the theoretical models for such representations and transformations; (b) specialized knowledge of the design characteristics, limitations, and potential applications of systems having the ability to transform information, and of broad areas of applications of computing which have common structures, processes, and techniques; and (c) knowledge of relevant mathematical and statistical sciences.Typical functions performed by Computer Scientists include:--development of software systems using a knowledge of techniques, procedures, and processes such as operating system theory, data structure, computer system architecture, Software engineering, and computer communications--development of computer graphic systems using a knowledge of graphic display systems, general purpose graphics languages, and optimization techniques involving preprocessors graphical algorithms, memory management methods, and high-speed communication links--development of high-speed computing systems and real time data acquisition systems--development of integrated computer systems using a knowledge of computer software and hardware concepts, and mathematics--development of problem-oriented and nonprocedural languages and their translating/operating systems, construction of input-output buffering schemes, and design of automatic scheduling and monitoring methods to increase scope and effectiveness of computer applications--development of advanced concepts of automation and information processing display, control and transfer</job_description>
      <location>Corona, CA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>(800)378-4559</phone_number>
      <salary>$49,765 to $133,967</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-09-30</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474427200</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>a3873288de94a795420ce5512a870f51</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474427200</page_url>
      <job_title>IT SPECIALIST (SYSADMIN)</job_title>
      <job_description>The primary purpose of this position is to serve as a Systems Administrator, planning and coordinating the installation, testing, operation, troubleshooting, and maintenance of hardware and software systems.
	Analyzes processes and problems relative to the design of systems and develops and recommends corrective action.
	Enhances automated systems to improve system response time for users.
	Develops and documents systems administration standard operating procedures and provides guidance to management.
	Provides technical assistance, a systems advisory service and training</job_description>
      <location>Lackland AFB, TX</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Air Force</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Air Force</organization>
      <phone_number>1-800-525-0102</phone_number>
      <salary>$61,748 to $80,270</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474415500</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>86c5578d691534c05206eddd8d0f5730</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474415500</page_url>
      <job_title>IT SPECIALIST (INFOSEC)</job_title>
      <job_description>As an IT Specialist (INFOSEC), you will perform the following duties:

	Perform JAVA updates when required for GFEBS interface.
	Responsible for ensuring all servers and workstations within Directorate of Public Works (DPW) have the latest security patches installed.
	Assist and support all Directorate of Public Works (DPW) computer users.
	Collaborate with DPW local area network (LAN) administrator and other technical personnel to maintain connectivity.
	Make recommendations regarding programming, hardware, software, and connectivity for long-range planning.</job_description>
      <location>Fort Hood, TX</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$56,226 to $73,098</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474115100</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>1b11b7cc6720c3b98a3dea791cf50fa9</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474115100</page_url>
      <job_title>Interdisciplinary Engineer</job_title>
      <job_description>Analyzes
trends in performance indicator scores to assist the Chief Engineer (CE)
with managing Agency level performance indicators, recommending corrective
action, establishing lessons learned, and influencing the improvement of
contractor processes. Analyzes contractor performance data including systems
engineering, software engineering, manufacturing engineering, supply chain
management, industrial analysis, and Earned Value Management (EVM) performance
for trends, and provides pertinent data to the CE.Evaluation
of production engineering effort, ability to produce, logistics, support
programs, master engineering planning schedules, special tooling, test
equipment, facilities and material review of nonconforming hardware. Provides
technical advice and consultation in relation to Independent Research and
Development Bid and Proposal expenses, first article inspections, production,
plant layout, manufacturing processes and techniques, and contract schedule
changes. Plans, executes, and documents surveillance of design, development,
and production efforts at contractor facilities on behalf of the Contract
Management Office (CMO) using the performance indicators identified in DCMA
engineering surveillance processes.Performs
all work in accordance with agency policies, standards, metrics and standard
operating procedures for effective contract administration of Department of Defense
(DoD) acquisitions.Prepares,
provides, and evaluates documentation regarding specific engineering and
manufacturing questions requiring resolution. Provides inputs for status
briefings to leadership, outlining assigned programs, projects, problems, and
recommended resolution.</job_description>
      <location>Hazelwood, MO</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Defense</sector>
      <organization>Department of Defense</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$72,651 to $94,449</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-24</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474483400</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>abea3ad2b30cc4675bdeeb86b2d8db6e</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474483400</page_url>
      <job_title>Nurse Practitioner or Physician Assistant (Medicine)</job_title>
      <job_description>The Nurse Practitioner (NP) or Physician Assistant (PA) will manage the Protocol Titration Clinic for Cardiology patients.  The purpose of the clinic is to increase access to care for Veterans transitioning from inpatient care to home.  The cardiovascular team will consist of a physician, mid-level practitioner, and a registered nurse.  The goal of the team is to improve access to specialty care, reduce recidivism, and to assist the provider with managing medications and chronic diseases.  The development of protocols for national protocols, training, mentorship guidelines and competencies will allow the focus of the clinic to be on specialty access for patients and same day referrals.  The Durham VA is one of the fastest growing facilities in the country servicing close to 1 million unique visits per year. Two-thirds of the Veteran populations have a cardiovascular diagnosis of sorts. This individual is delegated the authority and responsibility in his/her area of expertise to assume major clinical, consultative, educational, research, and administrative duties and assignments related to the care of cardiology patients.  Functions or Scope of Assigned Duties:  The following description covers the most significant duties performed but does not exclude other responsibilities, which may be assigned.Clinical (Approximately 85%)1. Works with the RN in the RN Protocol Titration clinic for cardiac patients.  Cardiology patients who will be seen in this telework clinic include patients needing titration if diuretics, titration of guideline based medications for hypertension and congestive heart failure.2. Coordinates and case manages same day heart failure clinic visits in decompensating patients.  The patients are in the recovery unit where IV diuretic therapy is utilized and care will continue with mid-level provider as outpatients.3. The mid-level provider will support and participate in research and consultation as needed4. Promotes secondary heart disease prevention with patient and family education5. Participates in discharge planning with transition of identified heart failure patients to a case managed outpatient setting with cardiology6. Team collaboration is utilized to approach congestive heart failure care of veterans by establishing safe and cost effective hospital length of stay in an interdisciplinary setting.Administrative (Approximately 15%)1. The program coordinator will collect and maintain data for quality improvement initiatives for heart failure2. Maintain the disease specific database, analyze and synthesize data, and facilitate performance improvement initiatives.3. Oversight of the implementation of the clinical practice guidelines for cardiac diseaseSupervisory Controls:The incumbent is directly responsible to the Chief, Cardiology Section and/or designee.Work Schedule: Monday-Friday, 8 hours between 0730 to 1730Functional Statement Title: Nurse Practitioner or Physician Assistant</job_description>
      <location>Durham, NC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Months</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(919)286-6858</phone_number>
      <salary>$70,602 to $135,097</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474050900</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>3771710f88bf36fada80d8367d822465</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474050900</page_url>
      <job_title>Registered Nurse - Community Living Center</job_title>
      <job_description>The 4 (four) key quality characteristics of the Relief RN role are: 1. Clinical knowledge and skills2. Rehab/restorative nursing abilities 3. Compliance with infection control guidelines4. Critical thinking and care planningThe Relief Nurse is responsible for the following:Performing dressing changes and treatments consistent with medical orders and protocolsRecommending PU management strategies, to include pressure relieving devicesProviding education to Providers and nursing staffAssessing residents for restorative nursing needs and developing the restorative plan of careMonitoring restorative and nursing staff execution of the restorative planPerforming as relief nurse on the neighborhoods, to include acting as charge nurse or patient care assistantOther duties as assignedWork Schedule: Multiple Tours Available - Some Weekend Rotations.Functional Statement Title/#: Staff Nurse</job_description>
      <location>Durham, NC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(919)286-6894</phone_number>
      <salary>$54,846 to $109,909</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474423200</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>3b6fc332021f89594d078cd626bea594</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474423200</page_url>
      <job_title>HUMAN RESOURCES SPECIALIST (EMPL REL/LABOR REL)</job_title>
      <job_description>The successful selectee will perform the following duties:

	Advise managers on the application of civilian personnel policies and procedures in labor relations matters (e.g., discipline, grievances, appeals, fair employment practices).
	Review completed disciplinary actions for compliance with regulations or local policy.
	Negotiate with senior leaders to determine a course of action for human resources issues.
	Brief managers and supervisors on performance management techniques (e.g., evaluation, feedback, recognition).
	Collaborate with management and unions to resolve unfair labor practice charges, grievances, workplace issues.</job_description>
      <location>Washington Navy Yard, DC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>800-378-4559</phone_number>
      <salary>$44,941 to $58,428</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474448200</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>9a9fb33fed7037a537a73236fec05d01</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474448200</page_url>
      <job_title>Civil Engineer</job_title>
      <job_description>Applies experience and advanced knowledge of civil engineering principles, theories, and concepts to accomplish assignments and to develop plans and techniques to improve programs and policies. Understand how his/her technical area interacts with or is affected by other disciplines and considers the objectives of the FAA Logistic Center when developing, integrating and implementing solutions to diverse, complex problems. Typical assignments may include: calculating loads and stresses on structures; investigating the strength of foundations beams; determining whether or not a structure can function safely; and shared responsibility for project/program management.Reviews construction plans of structures and facilities that support the mission. Performs Contracting Officer Representative (COR) duties, and a variety of technical duties involving designing, constructing, and maintaining structures and facilities in accordance with local/state construction code. Works in a professional team environment engaged in researching, developing and evaluating new criteria and methodology in structural engineering.Duties may also include developing or approving technical specifications, design plans, or engineering standards. Creates designs and approves construction to local/state codes and or ordinances. This work involves investigating and resolving unique structural engineering problems thought applied structural engineering knowledge such as mechanics, hydraulics, structures, materials, engineering geology and surveying.Specific experience with the tower structures, foundations, and anchors is valuable to this position. Familiarity with tower structural analysis software and computer-aided design (CAD) software is desirable. Will generate project closeout documentation. COR reports, joint acceptance inspections (JAI) reports, contractor acceptance inspections (CAI) reports, participates in the creation of CAD drawings, and provide relines for "as built" and revisions.Responsible for project development including but not limited to engineering and cost estimates for complete projects involving the design, installation, fabrication, engineering change repair, or engineering evaluation of structures and facilities.Provides guidance to lower-level staff to solve difficult technical issues. Resolves all but unique technical problems without the intervention of management or a more experienced engineer. Identifies and informs management of problems that require their attention. Often develops and recommends techniques to address problem situations.This position may require a special security level to support CBP programs.Physical: Heavy lifting (over 45 lbs.), heavy carrying (over 45 lbs.) straight pulling 2 hours, pulling hand over hand 1hour, reaching above shoulder, use of fingers, both hands required, walking 1 hour, standing 3 hours, kneeling 2 hours, climbing legs-only 2 hours, climbing use of legs and arms, both legs required, operation of crane, truck, tractor, or motor vehicle, ability for rapid mental and muscular coordination simultaneously, near vision correctable at 13" to 16" Jaeger 1 to 4, far vision correctible in one eye to 20/20 and to 20/40 in the other, both eyes required, depth perception, ability to distinguish shades of colors, hear (aid permitted).Environmental: Outside and inside, excessive heat, excessive cold, excessive humidity, excessive dampness or chilling, dry atmospheric conditions, excessive noise (intermittent), dust, fumes, smoke or gasses, solvents, grease, and oils, radiant energy, electrical energy, slipper or uneven walking surfaces, working around machinery with moving parts, working around moving objects or vehicles, working on ladders or scaffolding, vibration, working closely with others, working alone, protracted or irregular hours of work.</job_description>
      <location>Oklahoma City, OK</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Transportation</sector>
      <organization>Department of Transportation</organization>
      <phone_number>405-954-7958</phone_number>
      <salary>$72,435 to $112,263</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474447600</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>30155af19ee38cb85bf0abe83652c2ed</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474447600</page_url>
      <job_title>Civil Engineer</job_title>
      <job_description>Applies experience and advanced knowledge of civil engineering principles, theories, and concepts to accomplish assignments and to develop plans and techniques to improve programs and policies. Understand how his/her technical area interacts with or is affected by other disciplines and considers the objectives of the FAA Logistic Center when developing, integrating and implementing solutions to diverse, complex problems. Typical assignments may include: calculating loads and stresses on structures; investigating the strength of foundations beams; determining whether or not a structure can function safely; and shared responsibility for project/program management.Reviews construction plans of structures and facilities that support the mission. Performs Contracting Officer Representative (COR) duties, and a variety of technical duties involving designing, constructing, and maintaining structures and facilities in accordance with local/state construction code. Works in a professional team environment engaged in researching, developing and evaluating new criteria and methodology in structural engineering.Duties may also include developing or approving technical specifications, design plans, or engineering standards. Creates designs and approves construction to local/state codes and or ordinances. This work involves investigating and resolving unique structural engineering problems thought applied structural engineering knowledge such as mechanics, hydraulics, structures, materials, engineering geology and surveying.Specific experience with the tower structures, foundations, and anchors is valuable to this position. Familiarity with tower structural analysis software and computer-aided design (CAD) software is desirable. Will generate project closeout documentation. COR reports, joint acceptance inspections (JAI) reports, contractor acceptance inspections (CAI) reports, participates in the creation of CAD drawings, and provide relines for "as built" and revisions.Responsible for project development including but not limited to engineering and cost estimates for complete projects involving the design, installation, fabrication, engineering change repair, or engineering evaluation of structures and facilities.Provides guidance to lower-level staff to solve difficult technical issues. Resolves all but unique technical problems without the intervention of management or a more experienced engineer. Identifies and informs management of problems that require their attention. Often develops and recommends techniques to address problem situations.This position may require a special security level to support CBP programs.Physical: Heavy lifting (over 45 lbs.), heavy carrying (over 45 lbs.) straight pulling 2 hours, pulling hand over hand 1hour, reaching above shoulder, use of fingers, both hands required, walking 1 hour, standing 3 hours, kneeling 2 hours, climbing legs-only 2 hours, climbing use of legs and arms, both legs required, operation of crane, truck, tractor, or motor vehicle, ability for rapid mental and muscular coordination simultaneously, near vision correctable at 13" to 16" Jaeger 1 to 4, far vision correctible in one eye to 20/20 and to 20/40 in the other, both eyes required, depth perception, ability to distinguish shades of colors, hear (aid permitted).Environmental: Outside and inside, excessive heat, excessive cold, excessive humidity, excessive dampness or chilling, dry atmospheric conditions, excessive noise (intermittent), dust, fumes, smoke or gasses, solvents, grease, and oils, radiant energy, electrical energy, slipper or uneven walking surfaces, working around machinery with moving parts, working around moving objects or vehicles, working on ladders or scaffolding, vibration, working closely with others, working alone, protracted or irregular hours of work.</job_description>
      <location>Oklahoma City, OK</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Transportation</sector>
      <organization>Department of Transportation</organization>
      <phone_number>405-954-7958</phone_number>
      <salary>$72,435 to $112,263</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474388900</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>e8ad0b4f219ca503377cff080976cc7f</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474388900</page_url>
      <job_title>Registered Nurse - Risk Manager</job_title>
      <job_description>The duties of the Registered Nurse, Risk Manager will include, but are not limited to:    1.  Serves as Risk Manager in the Quality Management Department. Directs and manages an integrated Risk Management Program that supports the mission, goals and objectives of the facility, and VHA. Provides guidance, consultation, and staff assistance in program reviews.     2.  Reviews and evaluates risk on all patient incident reports and provide clinical advice on clinic management practices, analytical tools, and problem solving approaches. Utilizes current trends and relevant theory to identify, analyze, and resolve problem areas in risk management for clinical practice.   3.  Provide a clinical review and manages the administrative tort claim review process at the facility level in collaboration with Chief of Staff, Regional Counsel, the Assistant U.S. Attorney, and the Office of Medical Legal Affairs as appropriate.   4.  Develops and maintains expertise/certification in area of clinical practices through attendance at continuing education sessions, conferences and workshops.   5.  Analyzes and evaluates, on a quantitative or qualitative basis, the effectiveness of programs or operations in meeting established goals, objectives and compliance with VHA policy, The Joint Commission standards and other internal and external regulatory agency requirements. Monitors and analyzes program performance data to determine program effectiveness and identify opportunities for program improvement.   6.  Provides oversight and clinical reviews for implementation of the Full Disclosure process to ensure compliance with administrative requirements. Develops and leads educational activities to enhance the clinical understanding and utilization of the Full Disclosure process by Executive Management and other health care professionals. Maintains database of full disclosure activities.   7.  Provides oversight for the Peer Review Program, complete clinical assessment reviews, effectively tracks and processes peer reviews according to VALBHS policy and provides technical support to the Peer Review Committee. Maintains database of peer review activities.   8.   Serves as resource/consultant on facility and Network committees/task forces that focus on risk management, performance improvement, policy/procedure development and compliance activities.   9.  Collaborates with the Chief, Quality Management for prevention of clinical risks throughout the medical facility. Develops effective relationships with clinical staff and administrative personnel from patient services to facilitate the delivery of patient care.   10. Assists facility leadership in the setting of institutional priorities related to the Risk Program Management.   11. Plans, develops and conducts education and training programs related to Risk Management, and related quality management topics. This includes New Employee Orientation, Resident Orientation, and ongoing education for staff at all levels throughout the organization.   12. Ensures application of institutional policies, especially those regarding patient rights, confidentiality and full disclosure. Serves as a resource and advocate for protection of patient and family rights.   13. Organizational Analysis: Collects, aggregates, and trends data for Healthcare Groups and Committees. Evaluates processes or makes recommendations based on data for effective organizational changes. Performs organizational analysis and utilizes current trends and relevant theory to identify, analyze and resolve problem areas in Risk Management.    14. Serves as a member of the Integrative Ethics Committee, Peer Review Committee, and Disturb Behavior Committee.   15. Serves as the facility clinical consultant and subject matter expert regarding: Peer Reviews, Full Disclosure, and Tort Claims.Functional Statements:  Dated 6/25/2014: Nurse 1, Level 1; Nurse 1, Level 2; Nurse 1, Level 3; Nurse 2; and Nurse 3Work Schedule: Monday through Friday, 8AM to 430PM</job_description>
      <location>Birmingham, AL</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(205)933-8101x4088</phone_number>
      <salary>$48,004 to $90,293</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474410900</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>3122e85ef0e74846a507da106c15cc53</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474410900</page_url>
      <job_title>Nurse (Clinical/Obstetrics-Gynecology)</job_title>
      <job_description>As a Nurse (Clinical/Obstetrics-Gynecology) you will:Provide specialized and comprehensive antepartum, intrapartum and postpartum nursing care to normal to high-risk obstetric patients.Independently determine and implement proper emergency interventions within scope of practice after identifying and interpreting maternal and/or fetal distress.Administer complex medications by any route as ordered.Utilize the nursing process to formulate a nursing plan of care relative to patients physiological, psychological, and sociological condition in order to provide ongoing and in depth assessment of patient problems, strengths and limitations.Operate or monitor the performance of sophisticated equipment used in the care of compromised neonates.</job_description>
      <location>Fort Wainwright, AK</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$93,363 to $118,570</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474205100</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>eabeaeb7f1b2c449bd9a48c10857248d</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474205100</page_url>
      <job_title>Mechanical Engineer, GS-12</job_title>
      <job_description>Performs mechanical engineering design and review work for both Host Nation and US funded projects in support of Army, Navy, Air Force, Marines and other official agencies. Projects cover mechanical engineering problems ranging from the conventional to the complex and require a capability of adapting precedence and engineering theories and principles to the particular needs of the project. Projects includes missile assembly buildings, communication facilities, family quarters, bachelor quarters, fire stations, theaters, chapels, service clubs, dental clinics, dispensaries, hospitals, commissaries, warehouses, ammunition storage facilities, precision measuring equipment, laboratories, hangars, power plants, POL facilities, hydrant fueling systems, boiler plants, etc. Projects are the reviews for overall soundness of mechanical engineering in a variety of special areas, such as heating, plumbing, air conditioning, refrigeration, fire protection, etc. Performs design work on projects, including design analysis and contract plans and specifications for U.S. funded projects and Host Nation funded projects.</job_description>
      <location>Zama, Camp Zama, Japan</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$64,813 to $83,632</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-28</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474457100</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>944d386b63bc98be3461535b08ba3779</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474457100</page_url>
      <job_title>Registered Nurse (AM&amp;CC)</job_title>
      <job_description>The Louis Stokes Cleveland Veterans Affairs Medical Center is recruiting for a Registered Nurse.  The Registered Nurse will function in the Access Management &amp; Care Coordination (AM&amp;CC) section in Patient Care Administrative Service.  The Registered Nurse duties include: Providing indirect nursing care to patients with complex needs as related to consult management, telephone triage.Collaborating with multiple departments to utilize resources effectively to provide high quality Veteran care.Utilizing clinical protocols, decision support tools, and appropriate resources to guide, assess, and recommend course of action.Implementing the nursing process to assess and identify areas for quality improvement or enhanced customer service.Participating in educational activities and staff meetings to improve clinical knowledge and enhance role performance and performance expectations.Communicating the plan of care/transfer to the patient, providers, and/or appropriate care team.Assisting the Program Support Assistants in collecting Veteran information to aid in Veteran care.Collaborating with physicians/unit Directors and Service Chiefs regarding Veteran care and unit activities.Applying critical thinking skills to solve clinical and administrative issues.Providing clinical management of all Care in the Community programs to include traditional Non-VA Care Consults, Patient Centered Community Care (PC3) and VA Choice.Determining clinical service assignments, timely patient communication, consult management and medical record review/retrieval.Serving as VA Choice Champion, to include service planning and education on the program and providing education and answers to patients regarding the program.Work Schedule: Monday through Friday 8:00 a.m. - 4:30 p.m.Relocation Expenses:  Relocation expenses are not authorized for this position.</job_description>
      <location>Cleveland, OH</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Only</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(216)791-2300x2150</phone_number>
      <salary>$60,732 to $112,751</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-31</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474004200</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>2e35010db792c1fb317615d15b1ff0f9</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474004200</page_url>
      <job_title>CONTRACT SPECIALIST</job_title>
      <job_description>The successful selectee will perform the following duties:

	Perform quality control on pre-award documents necessary for contract award (e.g., performance work statements, cost estimates, acquisition strategies, source selection plans, determination and finding, justification and approval of sole source solicitation) to ensure requirements are met in both competitive and sole source environments.
	Oversee contracts by monitoring contract performance, preparing modifications, and determining the necessary course of action to comply with terms.
	Negotiate changes (e.g., extensions of delivery schedules, price adjustments, labor hours, terms and conditions, overhead rates) resulting from contract modifications.
	Conduct price and cost analysis to determine reasonableness of price to make recommendations for the award.
	Create solicitations, awards, and contract modifications using procurement systems for the command.</job_description>
      <location>Bethesda, MD</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>800-378-4559</phone_number>
      <salary>$79,720 to $103,639</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/473109400</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>bec05222e13d6d07e2a2fdaf9437c095</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/473109400</page_url>
      <job_title>Supervisory Interdisciplinary</job_title>
      <job_description>Plan, direct, monitor, execute, and supervise staff on pertinent technical provisions of complex programs essential to the mission.Maintain program and administrative reference materials, project files, and relevant background documents.Establish program and performance goals, priorities, and major work schedules.Determine long-range manpower requirements.Participate as the technical representative, in periodic inspections of all field installations.Perform liaison work with design elements on engineering problems requiring coordination.Review work plans from field projects for technical and compliance requirements.</job_description>
      <location>Saint Louis, MO</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$86,391 to $112,306</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-24</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474323200</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>b9dde2fdaafe3a83e88af8dcb7c3e955</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474323200</page_url>
      <job_title>Survey Statistician, GS-1530-13, Census-DOC-WKD</job_title>
      <job_description>The individual selected for this position will:Work with a variety of internal and external customers (Federal, State, Local and private industry).Manage projects and engage staff and stakeholders using project management skills.Develop and implement data collection plans, processes, and strategies according to the survey sponsor’s requirements.Access, analyze, and review statistical data, programs, and training materials.</job_description>
      <location>District of Columbia, DC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Commerce</sector>
      <organization>Department of Commerce</organization>
      <phone_number>301-763-3705</phone_number>
      <salary>$94,796 to $123,234</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-24</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474454000</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>10449f28efbe192890d1dd593e5aa754</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474454000</page_url>
      <job_title>Registered Nurse - Infection Control</job_title>
      <job_description>The Infection Control Coordinator  responsibilities will include, but not limited to, the following:             ·         Accountable for surveillance of infections and reporting.·         Serves as a consultant to individual Care Lines for infection prevention and control issues and events.·         Facilitates the development of prevention and control activities and presents specific continuing education programs and facility wide orientation.·         Generates reports to input, extract, trend and analyze pertinent data and presents them to committees assigned.·         Conducts outbreak investigations, provides feedback on analysis  of data to clinical staff ·         Develops patient education tools and actively participates in patient education·         Exhibits leadership and team process skills when collaborating with care/service lines for program development, implementation and evaluation.·         Participates as part of educator and other teaching responsibilities as assigned.·         Maintains current knowledge relevant to the principles of infection control and epidemiology.·         Serve as a liaison with the city, state, county and health departments for communicable disease reporting and follow up.Work Schedule: 8:00a.m. - 4:30p.m. -  Mon - FriFunctional Statement Title/#:  Infection Control</job_description>
      <location>Houston, TX</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Only</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(713)791-1414x6526</phone_number>
      <salary>$60,552 to $114,754</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-28</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474492900</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>eedda86627d350ea83c37bf9f20a9da1</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474492900</page_url>
      <job_title>Advanced Practice Nurse-PC-MHI</job_title>
      <job_description>The
Advanced Practice Registered Nurse executes position responsibilities that
demonstrate leadership, experience, and creative approaches to the management
of complex client care. The incumbent functions autonomously within a defined
scope of practice and ongoing collaboration with physician and
interdisciplinary team.

The
incumbent is a member of the Primary Care- Mental Health integration team
assigned to provide co-located collaborative care to promote effective
treatment of common mental health conditions in the primary care environment
(e.g. mild to moderate depression, problem drinking, anxiety, adjustment
disorders). Responsibilities include screening and assessment, diagnosis,
pharmacological interventions, individual counseling, and consultation with
PACT team to address treatment needs.

Work Schedule: Monday-Friday, evenings and
weekends as needed.

Functional Statement Title/#:APRN NII</job_description>
      <location>Saint Cloud, MN</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(320)255-6301</phone_number>
      <salary>$77,035 to $130,660</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-21</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474108700</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>e68e03eec1caa854677f20bb4f5d7a23</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474108700</page_url>
      <job_title>INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPECIALIST (APPSW/NETWORK)</job_title>
      <job_description>The successful selectee will perform the following duties:

	Provide resources to support TEAM members in the delivery of all Integrated Logistics Support (ILS) elements by providing, maintaining, and developing the necessary logistics information systems and tools.
	Ensure full life cycle support for the entire U.S. Navy and Marine Corps NAVAIR Fleet Systems Array (NFSA) assets from cradle to grave.
	Identify, document, validate and verify, control, report and record the functional and physical characteristics of all assets controlled by the NFSA program.
	Assist Information Processes and Technology (IPT) in managing the development, processing, approval, and implementation of the NFSA program, with consideration to all the technical, financial, logistics and programmatic components.
	Provide assistance to the program Management Office, to ensure that the NFSA approach is developed and implemented in accordance with the DOD, U.S. Navy and NAVAIR policies and procedures.</job_description>
      <location>Patuxent River, MD</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>800-378-4559</phone_number>
      <salary>$94,796 to $123,234</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-21</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474424000</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>b56ec7766a1974bf7b62fda76e26bdd6</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474424000</page_url>
      <job_title>CLINICAL NURSE</job_title>
      <job_description>The successful selectee will perform the following duties:

	You will address medical issues with emphasis on prevention of disease and promotion of health and wellness
	You will provide guidance and direction to ancillary personnel
	You will ensure the standards of ambulatory care nursing practice are met
	You will perform functions of a utilization and case management nurse
	You will implement and oversee a Health Promotion Program</job_description>
      <location>China Lake, CA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>800-378-4559</phone_number>
      <salary>$84,376 to $107,149</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474499500</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>2d683d99a5c53df7e73fa95267713dda</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474499500</page_url>
      <job_title>IT Specialist Customer Maintenance</job_title>
      <job_description>The Information Technonology Specialist independently installs and maintains computer related hardware and troubleshoots system problems in support of various Personal and Family Readiness (PFRD) application programs that affect accuracy, reliability, acceptability and timeliness of final work products.  Provides analysis and troubleshooting support to users and supports IT Specialists in program analysis, design, development, testing and implementation for applications.  Installs, maintains and troubleshoots PC / LAN hardware to include: CPU’s, monitors, printers, LAN cabling, modems, laptops, switches, hubs, UPS’s, keyboards, mice and other hardware devices.  Maintains and tracks asset inventories.  Maintains and tracks software library.  Creates and maintains Standard Operating Procedures documentation and how to guides.  Maintains and updates call center ticket tracking software knowledge base and other related documentation.  Provides end user PC / LAN hardware and software support through telephone, email and desk side support utilizing a call center ticket request.  Creates and maintains image library.  Unpacks, configures and deploys PCs.  Installs and configures Blackberry and other PDA’s.  Maintains and distributes mobile computing library.  Maintains and distributes projectors.  Provides backup and restores operations on user directories.  Maintains and supports printers.  Initiates contact with internal support groups, commands, field personnel, outside vendors and others for problem identification and resolution.Provides World Class Customer Service with an emphasis on customer centricity, professionalism and courtesy. Assists customers and communicates in a professional manner by investigating issues, conflicts and problems to provide resolution in a timely manner. Alerts the higher-level supervisor, or proper point of contact for help when problems arise.  Adheres to safety regulations and standards.  Promptly reports any observed workplace hazards, and any injury, occupational illness, and/or property damage resulting from workplace mishaps to the immediate supervisor. Adheres to established standards of actively supporting the principles of the EEO program and prevention of sexual harassment.Performs other related duties as assigned.  This is a mixed position where the incumbent must be able to lift and carry objects up to 45lbs independently and objects over 45lbs with assistance.</job_description>
      <location>Kansas City, MO</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Navy</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Navy</organization>
      <phone_number>703/432-0435</phone_number>
      <salary>$38,000 to $48,000</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-30</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474505300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>6518997a72ecae5193344db78bb827d8</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474505300</page_url>
      <job_title>Human Resources Specialist</job_title>
      <job_description>Administers all in-service placement including IHS programs, promotions, reassignments, details, etc.Provides assistance to all applicants regarding placement with both the IHS and other Federal agencies.Receives SF-52 recruitment requests, reviews attached position description, and solicits additional occupational and position information from requesting official. Works with the requesting and selecting officials to develop knowledge, skills and abilities statements.Prepare vacancy announcements.Receives and examines applications to makes qualification analysis.Coordinate Title 38, pay flexibilities for Recruitment, Relocation and Retention bonuses, above the minimum rate.</job_description>
      <location>Bemidji, MN</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Health And Human Services</sector>
      <organization>Department of Health And Human Services</organization>
      <phone_number>(218)444-0456</phone_number>
      <salary>$60,210 to $78,270</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474376100</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>2054fd43483013a4949f8a8cb02ccaab</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474376100</page_url>
      <job_title>Physical Scientist, ZP-1301-III (GS-11/12 Equivalent)</job_title>
      <job_description>As an equipment engineer, the incumbent will perform duties in support of the CNST NanoFab, including:Troubleshoot and repair complex systems on a wide variety of NanoFab equipment including sputter deposition, electron beam deposition, reactive ion etching, low pressure chemical vapor deposition, plasma enhanced chemical vapor deposition, oxidation/diffusion furnaces, optical lithography, and high purity gas cabinets and gas distribution systems.Perform design work for new, renovation, and improvement projects for NanoFab equipment and facility control systems, including novel interlock systems.Interpret and adapt traditional methods and approaches in developing design calculations, layouts, drawings, and specifications that support project objectives and standards.Prepare conceptual studies and sketches that indicate pertinent design features, material, equipment, and specifications.Coordinate projects with engineers in other disciplines or with architects.Keep abreast of emerging technologies to ensure programmed development will not prematurely become obsolete.</job_description>
      <location>Gaithersburg, MD</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Commerce</sector>
      <organization>Department of Commerce</organization>
      <phone_number>301-975-8212</phone_number>
      <salary>$66,510 to $103,639</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474224800</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>9f971fb2c428ed86826b1ce87a65f6ef</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474224800</page_url>
      <job_title>Nurse (Administrative)</job_title>
      <job_description>As a Nurse (Administrative) you will:Coordinate with clinics and services and the medical screening process to assist patientsin pre-certification for hospitalization.Advise insurance company of impending patient admissions.Obtain authorization for treatment under the respective insurance coverage.Provide rationale/justification for hospitalization, the services to be furnished and thetreatment to be rendered.Assist in the development of protocols and procedures applicable to utilizationmanagement efforts dealing with third party reimbursements.</job_description>
      <location>Fort Bliss, TX</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$60,128 to $76,354</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474224300</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>122a43a85b3fe5c56e3d5349141eecb4</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474224300</page_url>
      <job_title>Biologist ZP-0401-III (GS-11/12 Equivalent)</job_title>
      <job_description>The incumbent will develop metrology to authoritatively access difficult genomic variant types in difficult regions of the human genome to meet stakeholder needs for benchmarking genome sequencing. Develop methods to use benchmarking results to assess strengths and weaknesses of methods and predict performance for variants of clinical interest. Work with Genome in a Bottle Consortium and Joint Initiative for Metrology in Biology communities to develop and disseminate methods for benchmarking human genome sequencing for clinical and research applications. Identify and develop additional whole genome reference samples, including samples for benchmarking tumor sequencing.</job_description>
      <location>Stanford, CA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>months)</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Commerce</sector>
      <organization>Department of Commerce</organization>
      <phone_number>301-975-8198</phone_number>
      <salary>$72,303 to $112,665</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-20</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474243800</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>3157647a788048f72e2b8184fd0130b5</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474243800</page_url>
      <job_title>Nurse (Clinical/Perioperative)</job_title>
      <job_description>As a Nurse (Clinical/Perioperative), you will, Assist anesthesiologists with complex procedures such as epidural catheter insertion, blood patches, and regional blocks.Provide comprehensive nursing care to patients based on nursing assessments and diagnoses, physician's medical care plan as well as the physical, mental, and emotional needs of the patient.Administer medications (oral, subcutaneous, intramuscular, intravenous), including potent narcotics, in accordance with physician's orders.Operate and monitor highly complex technical and specialized medical equipment.Independently determine and implement proper emergency measures after identifying and interpreting life-threatening conditions and initiating life-saving measures.</job_description>
      <location>Fort Riley, KS</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of the Army</sector>
      <organization>Department of the Army</organization>
      <phone_number>(000)000-0000</phone_number>
      <salary>$54,803 to $71,247</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-17</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474538500</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>9468738d45e395ee2da0616d474f60a6</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474538500</page_url>
      <job_title>Registered Nurse (RN), (Community Living Center)</job_title>
      <job_description>This position is located at the Portland VA Vancouver campus in the Rehabilitation Long Term Care (RLTC) Division. The Community Living Center(CLC) RN provides short term transitional care for residents who require skilled nursing care, close medical monitoring and sub-acute rehabilitation. Resident populations include those with CVA, Neurologic disorders, liver transplants, diabetics, and other chronic or sub-acute medical conditions. The RN is accountable for patient driven care of a defined group of residents. Based on education and experience, the RN may be assigned as a charge nurse, preceptor; or in the interdisciplinary leadership roles of Veteran Care Manager, Minimum Data Set Coordinator, or Admission Coordinator. The RN delivers fundamental, knowledge-based care to assigned clients while developing technical competencies. 
WORK SCHEDULE: Days, 6:00 am - 02:30 pm, every other weekend requiredFUNCTIONAL STATEMENT TITLE: Nurse I Level 1/2/3; Nurse II, Nurse III</job_description>
      <location>Vancouver, WA</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
      <sector>Department of Veterans Affairs</sector>
      <organization>Department of Veterans Affairs</organization>
      <phone_number>(414)255-6750</phone_number>
      <salary>$67,652 to $113,737</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-27</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474488700</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>1c33e428eebe81b98061905ded57491d</uniq_id>
      <job_board>https://www.usajobs.gov:443</job_board>
      <page_url>https://www.usajobs.gov:443/GetJob/ViewDetails/474488700</page_url>
      <job_title>Lead IT Specialist</job_title>
      <job_description>Oversees operational and program management responsibility for assuring implementation, administration, maintenance, and operation of all computing service platforms and monitoring of the FDIC enterprise system environments including VMware, Windows Server, Midrange UNIX and Linux and z/OS (Mainframe); Storage Subsystem Operation; and Capacity Management.Develops and follows policies, procedures, standards and guidelines and is responsible for the coordination of implementation, administration and maintenance activities as necessary with network, storage, servers and software throughout the Corporation in support of delivery of computing services and providing centralized situational awareness to the FDIC.</job_description>
      <location>Washington DC, DC</location>
      <country_code>US</country_code>
      <job_type>Full-Time</job_type>
      <phone_number>703-562-2584</phone_number>
      <salary>$142,071 to $236,815</salary>
      <country>United States</country>
      <date_added>2017-07-14</date_added>
      <has_expired>2017-07-28</has_expired>
</record>
</page>
</root>
